class Topic {
  final List _items = [
    {
      "category": "A+ 1001",
      "items": [
        // A Study
        "Troubleshooting printers",
        "Troubleshooting",
        "Resolving problems",
        "Virtualization",
        "Cloud Computing",
        "Printers",
        "SOHO Devices",
        "Custom PC configurations",
        "Common devices",
        "Power Supplies",
        "Working with peripheral devices",
        "Working with motherboards CPUs an Add-on cards",
        "Storage solutions",
        "Random access memory",
        "Connectors",
        "Basic cable types",
        "Networking tools",
        "Network types",
        "Networking",
        "Implementing network concepts",
        "TCP and UDP ports",
        "Network Hosts",
      ],
      "questions": [
        //Troubleshooting printers
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the most likely cause of a 13.4 error code on a LaserJet printer?",
              "answer": "paper jam",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements correctly represent characteristics and/or best practices of working with printer drivers? ",
              "answer":
                  "Drivers are not compatible between operating systems. Install the drivers before connecting the printer. & Download drivers for the manufacturers website",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Printer Output can different from another monitor display because?",
              "answer": "Monitors use RGB output printers use CMYK",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which method can be used to get more print jobs out of a LaserJet toner cartridge?",
              "answer": "Shake the cartridge",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "If printer reports its running low on memory what do you do?",
              "answer": "Turn the printer off and on again",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which conditions may result from or be addressed by upgrading the firmware of a printer?",
              "answer": "Improved performance & new features added",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which scenarios would be most likely to cause multiple pages to feed through a printer?",
              "answer": "Very thin paper and damp paper",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which step should always be performed first when attempting to clear a paper jam?",
              "answer": "Disconnect the power",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which information about a printer can be a ascertained by printing a test page?",
              "answer": "Printer model and driver list",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A blurry print job might result from which situation?",
              "answer": "Printing on the wrong side of the paper",
            },
            {
              "question": "Calibrating a printer addresses which issue?",
              "answer": "Color mismatch",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "If a user complains that they are not able to connect to a shared printer while several other users are able to connect successfully what is the most likely cause of this issue?",
              "answer": "The user does not permission to use the printer",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which print quality issue is likely to only be found on a laser printer?",
              "answer": "Ghost image",
            },
          ],
        },

        //Troubleshooting
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which factor is most likely responsible for unreliable or unstable Wi-Fi connection?",
              "answer": "Distance from access point",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "If a user reports that they have made some changes in the bios configuration of their system and now anytime they try to boot with a flash drive plugged in the system will not boot producing an operating system not found error would likely be the cause of this error?",
              "answer": "The user made a change to the boot sequence",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "If a user reports that their system has been periodically unstable and has reported some errors when opening and saving files what should be done first and as soon as possible?",
              "answer": "Back up the data",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which resolution would be most likely be the best option for an external monitor with dead pixels?",
              "answer": "Replace the monitor",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which hard drive attribute is not reported by SMART technology?",
              "answer": "Fragmentation",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which raid level will result in a data loss with the failure of only a single drive?",
              "answer": "0",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Why should special attention be given to the power of a laptop if you are assembling or disassembling it for service?",
              "answer":
                  "Because laptops have two power sources the power adapter & the battery",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "If two devices on the same network have the same address which situation results?",
              "answer": "IP conflict",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which resolution would most likely be required for a system that has blown capacitor’s?",
              "answer": "Replace the motherboard",
            },
          ],
        },

        //Resolving problems
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which activity would not be an effective means of identifying a problem?",
              "answer": "Assuming based on experience",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "If after re-creating an issue you have developed and tested a theory and evaluated the results to discover that the issue has been resolved what is the next step of the process?",
              "answer": "Develop a plan of action",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of documentation model refers to a source that is generally constructed and maintained by the user in an organization?",
              "answer": "wiki",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which component of a formal controlled change process allows for verifying that a change will be effective?",
              "answer": "Testing in the sandbox environment",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which scenario would be considered to be using external research or resources to address a problem?",
              "answer": "Contacting an application vendor",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Once a plan of action has been fully developed when should be implemented?",
              "answer": "Whenever the impact on operations is lowest",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Verifying fully restored functionality should be performed by which entities?",
              "answer":
                  "The user of the system. & The person who implemented the fix",
            },
          ],
        },

        //Virtualization
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which virtual machine resource setting often cannot be changed while the virtual machine is running?",
              "answer": "Memory",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of computing scenario most likely describes virtualization?",
              "answer":
                  "A single physical computer hosting multiple logical computers",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which feature of hypervisors distinguishes type 1 from type 2?",
              "answer":
                  "Type 2 has a local operating system installed on the host system",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of computing configuration can result in a much higher demand on your local area network when using virtualization?",
              "answer": "Virtual desktop infrastructure (VDI)",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which computing scenario would not be an example of effectively using virtual machines?",
              "answer":
                  "Supplying a user with a laptop to increase their mobility",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What functionality is provided by emulators in virtualization?",
              "answer":
                  "They intercept hardware request from the virtual machine and pass them to the physical machine",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Why should the security of a physical host machine be give additional consideration?",
              "answer":
                  "Because corruption of any virtual machine means corruption of the host",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "If you have a virtual machine running a 32 bit version of an operating system and it currently has 4GB of RAM configured, what level of performance boost should you expect if you allocate an additional 4GB?",
              "answer": "None",
            },
          ],
        },

        //Cloud Computing
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of organization is most likely to benefit from a PaaS cloud subscription?",
              "answer": "A software development house",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which types of resources would you be most likely to configure if your cloud subscription is primarily for laaS?",
              "answer":
                  "A load balancer. A virtual network. & A virtual machine",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which scenario best describes a resource pulling configuration?",
              "answer":
                  "Multiple databases sharing memory and processing among each other",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Why is security a primary concern before implementing cloud file storage services?",
              "answer": "The data is no longer in ur physica position",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The development and use of cloud-based applications is most categorized as which type of cloud service?",
              "answer": "PaaS. & SaaS",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which cloud services characteristic describes the on demand computing?",
              "answer":
                  "The ability of users to request new resources on their own",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A resource such as data on a virtual machine that can only be accessed by other virtual machines in the same cloud subscription describes what model of cloud resource sharing?",
              "answer": "Internal",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements about using cloud-based email are correct?",
              "answer":
                  "A browser is required on local devices. pay based on number of users",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A measure service helps u no property of a cloud application or service?",
              "answer":
                  "If enough servers have been implemented to handle the load",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "If your environment is using a SAS application that is access by all types of devices in your organization and an update is released, on which systems would you have to apply the update?",
              "answer": "None",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "If users connect to a pool of virtual machines to run an application or service and can be connected to any system at any time, which type of connection does this represent?",
              "answer": "Stateless",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A metered service ultimately helps to determine which characteristic of a cloud application or service?",
              "answer": "How much it will cost",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of cloud service would be most appropriate for an organization that provides resources to its own branch offices from a centralized corporate headquarters?",
              "answer": "Private",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which cloud services characteristic describes the nature of rapid elasticity?",
              "answer":
                  "The ability of resource to request or relinquish resources automatically",
            },
          ],
        },

        //Printers
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the most common type of material used with 3-D printers?",
              "answer": "Plastic",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which types of maintenance procedures can be performed on inkjet printer heads?",
              "answer": "Nozzle check. Head alignment. & Head cleaning",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What type of output is required for a virtual printer?",
              "answer": "A file name.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A dot matrix printer produces an image through which basically means?",
              "answer": "Impact",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "During which step of the laser printing process does toner get applied to the imaging drum?",
              "answer": "Developing",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A piezoelectric print head uses which configuration to force ink onto paper?",
              "answer": "A charged & vibrating Crystal",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Maintenance of a thermal printer typically involves which processes?",
              "answer":
                  "Cleaning print heads or heating elements. & cleaning dust and debris",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "calibration of a laser printer refers to which process?",
              "answer":
                  "Ensuring the print quality matches the display quality",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which component is to ultimately responsible for producing the image with thermal printing devices?",
              "answer": "The paper",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which component of laser printers responsible for ensuring the toner permanently adheres to the paper?",
              "answer": "Fusing assembly",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which possible danger should be taken into account when changing the printhead of a dot- matrix printer?",
              "answer": "Heat",
            },
          ],
        },

        //SOHO Devices
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "If a SOHO multifunction device has an integrated print server then which type of system would most likely NOT be found in a small business network?",
              "answer": "A dedicated server",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which printer configuration option refers to the ability of a device to print on both sides of the paper?",
              "answer": "Duplex",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements correctly describes the characteristics of cloud printing?",
              "answer":
                  "Only a connection to the Internet is required. no local drivers are necessary. print jobs are sent by an Internet service to the printer",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In a large centralized printer sharing network which operations should be performed to ensure that sensitive data is not obtained from previously submitted print jobs to the print server?",
              "answer":
                  "Delete all files from the printer spooler folder. Ensure that only select users are configured as print administrators",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of wireless configuration would allow all devices to access a SOHO multifunction device without pairing or using direct device to device communication?",
              "answer": "802.11 infrastructure mode",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of connections would you be most likely to find on the device end of a modern SOHO multifunction device?",
              "answer": "USB type B and ethernet",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which Proprietary wireless printing protocol is built into the iOS operating system?",
              "answer": "Airprint",
            },
          ],
        },

        //Custom PC configurations
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "If your audio/video editing process favors high capacity and very reliable storage which type of disk configuration would be best suited to your needs? RAID array Which component of a virtualized workstation should generally be given the most consideration in terms of performance and application needs?",
              "answer": "Memory and CPU",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which device of a graphic design workstation should generally be given the most consideration in terms of performance and application needs?",
              "answer": "Video card",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which feature of a thin client would generally still require relatively high performance?",
              "answer": "Network",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of custom PC configuration would most likely feature multiple monitors surround sound and robust cooling?",
              "answer": "Gaming PC",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements correctly describes the characteristics of a thick client?",
              "answer":
                  "Most applications are locally installed. they tend to have more ram. they have higher demands on local resources",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A home server PC could be described as emulating which type of storage service?",
              "answer": "NAS",
            },
          ],
        },

        //Common devices
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Applications from the window store can be run on which type of devices?",
              "answer": "Windows 10 desktop and windows 10 laptop",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "If attempting to connect to a previously used wireless network from a windows 10 laptop continually fails which operation should be performed first to correct the situation?",
              "answer":
                  "Choose forget for the wireless network and reconnect with new settings",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "If all of your clients systems are considered to be thick clients which function would a server most likely be performing?",
              "answer": "Data storage",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "if tapping on the touchscreen does not register in the correct location which action should be taken?",
              "answer": "The touchscreen should be calibrated",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "which examples of laptop users accounts would be considered to be Microsoft account?",
              "answer": "JohnDoe@Hotmail.com johndoe@Outlook.com",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of system would most likely be used as a thin client to run a line of business application?",
              "answer": "An old laptop computer",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "which type of information can typically be synchronize between devices running windows 10?",
              "answer": "The local data and configured settings",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "which Statements are correct about making configuration changes to your windows 10 system by using the Settings app versus using the control panel?",
              "answer": "Settings can be configured in either without conflict",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements are correct but configuring and using a touchpad?",
              "answer":
                  "Touchpads are almost always integrated into laptop computers",
            },
          ],
        },

        //Power Supplies
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question": "Which calculation is used to determine wattage?",
              "answer": "amps multiplied by volts",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "If the AC input of a power supply is listed at 110-240 V what does the indicate about the unit?",
              "answer": "It can be used in either North America or Europe",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which feature might you find on a 24-pin motherboard power connector that makes it backward compatible with older motherboards?",
              "answer": "A detachable 4-pin connector",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What type of power configuration would typically be found in the US and Canada?",
              "answer": "110 -120 Volts at 60 Hz",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of devices would most likely require 12 Volts of power?",
              "answer": "Fans, graphic cards, & a newer CPU",
            },
          ],
        },

        //Working with peripheral devices
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "In which scenario would you most likely find a VR headset in use?",
              "answer": "Computer gaming and training and simulations",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "To enable face-to-face communication on a desktop computer you should install which type of device?",
              "answer": "webCam",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "On which type of system would you most likely find a touchpad?",
              "answer": "Laptop computer",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The process of laserbeam focusing on the drum to drain off the electrical charge happens in which stage of the laser printing process?",
              "answer": "Exposing",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which types of connections would you most likely find for a mouse and keyboard in recent years?",
              "answer": "USB and wireless",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A chip reader that reads information by simply tapping the card to the reader is using which type of communication?",
              "answer": "NFC",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "NFC devices must be how close to one another for effective communication to occur?",
              "answer": "2-3 cm",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A modern flatbed scanner would most likely use which interface?",
              "answer": "USB",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A microphone and speakers would most likely be included as part of which type of device?",
              "answer": "A laptop computer",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "On which type of system would you most likely find an external optical drive?",
              "answer": "A newer laptop computer",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which types of external storage is no moving or mechanical parts?",
              "answer": "Flash drives and solid-state drives",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In which applications would you most likely find a smart card reader being used?",
              "answer":
                  "Reading bank or credit cards and gaining access to a secure facility",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Game controllers would most likely connect to your computer using which type of interface?",
              "answer": "USB",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "If monitor is described as being 27 inches what does the value indicate?",
              "answer": "The link of the screen on a diagonal",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In which scenario would you most likely find a KVM switch being used?",
              "answer":
                  "A network administrator managing several network servers",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The brightness of the lamp in the projector is indicated by whichvalue?",
              "answer": "Lumens",
            },
          ],
        },

        //Working with motherboards CPUs an Add-on cards
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "A passive heat sink would be implemented as which type of device or system?",
              "answer": "Radiator",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which motherboard expansion bus connector types were typically white and approximately 3 inches long?",
              "answer": "PCI",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which analogy would best equate to the process of a hyper threading?",
              "answer": "One person working on two tasks",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which characteristics of AMD processor’s might make them a better choice over Intel processors?",
              "answer":
                  "They are better suited to graphic-based applications and they are less expensive",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which security feature of BIOS security is implemented as a chip on the motherboard used to store encryption keys?",
              "answer": "TPM",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In which type of system would you be most likely to find micro ATX motherboard?",
              "answer": "A smaller desktop computer lying flat",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements correctly describes the characteristics of the basic input/output systems (BiOS) of a computer?",
              "answer":
                  "It can only be updated by overriding the entire BIOS and it is pre-installed by a motherboard manufacture",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of expansion card would be virtually required by a PC gamer?",
              "answer": "Video card",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement best describes the nature of a dual core processor?",
              "answer":
                  "There are two processing centers within a single CPU chip",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of device best describes a complementary metal oxide semi conductor (CMOS)?",
              "answer": "A storage device",
            },
          ],
        },

        //Storage solutions
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "What type of data would you most likely find on a Blu-ray Disc?",
              "answer": "High definition video and video games",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the storage capacity of a standard CD ROM disc?",
              "answer": "650-700 MB",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which characteristic of a solid-state drives uniquely distinguish them from magnetic hard drives?",
              "answer": "They have no moving parts",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In which scenario would magnetic hard drive be preferable to a solid-state drive?",
              "answer":
                  "When you need to archive a very large amount of data and when you want to store data for a very long time",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements are correct in terms of comparing 2.5 inch to 3.5 inch drives?",
              "answer":
                  "2.5 inch drives are generally quieter then 3.5 inch. 3.5 inch drives are generally faster than 2.5 inch. 3.5 inch drives are generally easier to install than 2.5 inch",
            },
            {
              "question": "Hybrid hard drives combine which two features?",
              "answer":
                  "The speed of solid-state drives and the capacity of hard disk drives",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Why might you choose to avoid backing up important data to a flash drive?",
              "answer":
                  "Because flash memory drives are easily lost and stolen",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which type of data is not supported on a DVD?",
              "answer": "High definition video",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A device is considered to be not swappable if it supports which characteristic?",
              "answer":
                  "It can be connected or disconnected without turning off the host computer",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which RAID level uses the parity calculation to allow for the reconstruction of lost data?",
              "answer": "5",
            },
          ],
        },

        //Random access memory
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "DDR2 refer to which performance characteristicas compared to DDR?",
              "answer": "It cycled twice as many times per bus cycle",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The clock cycle speed of SDRAM is determined by which factor?",
              "answer": "The speed of the system bus used by the system",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "How wide is memory bus on a system that uses single channel RAM?",
              "answer": "64 bits",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which physical characteristics distinguishes parity RAM chips from non-parity RAM chips?",
              "answer": "Parity ram chips have 9 modules non-parit have 8",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In which type of system would you most likely find SODIMM chip style?",
              "answer": "Laptop",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement best indicates the performance characteristics of a system using dual channel RAM?",
              "answer":
                  "Separate memory chips can be accessed simultaneously over each channel",
            },
            {
              "question": "DDR3 RAM cycles how many times per bus cycle?",
              "answer": "4",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which physical chip types were used with DDR4 RAM?",
              "answer": "256-pin SODIMM & 288-pin DIMM",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "ECC memory is able to perform which type of recovery when accessing data?",
              "answer":
                  "Detect & correct single bit errors for each byte written",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement best indicates the performance characteristics of a system using triple channelRAM?",
              "answer": "The total memory bus width is 192 bits",
            },
          ],
        },

        //Connectors
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "For which type of device would you most likely use a Molex connector?",
              "answer":
                  "Power interface for an internal hard drive. power interface for a CD ROM",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A BNC connector is most commonly found in use with which type of cable?",
              "answer": "Coaxial",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which Apple devices will support a lightning connector?",
              "answer": "iPad 4 & iPhone 5",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "For which implementations might you find an RJ 11 connector being used?",
              "answer": "A modem, a phone line, and ADSL Internet service.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "For which type of device would you most likely use an eSATA connector?",
              "answer": "Data interface for an external hard drive",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which connector is most commonly associated with an RS 232 interface?",
              "answer": "DB9",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "SCSI device connectors would more likely be found in use with which type of system?",
              "answer": "Servers",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which USB connector tape is reversible?",
              "answer": "C",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In which implementation would you most likely find an RG 6 connector?",
              "answer": "Connected to a digital TV",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which device would most likely use a DB9 connector?",
              "answer": "Mouse",
            }
          ],
        },

        //Basic cable types
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of video interface users packetized data transmissions?",
              "answer": "Display ports"
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of fiber optic cabling would be most appropriate to use to connect to branch offices that are many miles apart?",
              "answer": "Single mode"
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which USB specification introduced a transfer rate of 480 MBPS?",
              "answer": "2.0"
            },
            {
              "question":
                  ".Which coaxial cable limitation is best described as power being transmitted by the braided shielding?",
              "answer": "Ground loop"
            },
            {
              "question": "For which device would you use a lightning cable?",
              "answer": "iPhone 5"
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "How many devices are supported in a daisychain configuration when using thunderbolt cables?",
              "answer": "6"
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which category of cable would be appropriate for an ethernet network that requires speeds of up to 10 GBPS over distances of 100 meters?",
              "answer": "Cat 6a"
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Category 5 cable is limited to what transmission speed?",
              "answer": "100 Mbps"
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "If you needed to convert between digital and analog and analog video which adapter would be required?",
              "answer": "DVI-VGA"
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which device interface would be required if youwanted to install six hard drives into a server that were all using the same cables?",
              "answer": "SCSI"
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What function does the shielding provide in shielded twisted pair cabling?",
              "answer": "More resistance and interference"
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which transmission characteristics would best describe the properties of serial peripheral cables.",
              "answer":
                  "Generally used for small transfers. transmits more effectively over longer distances. transmits a single bit at a time",
            }
          ],
        },

        //Networking tools
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "In which scenario would you be most likely to use a punch down tool?",
              "answer":
                  "Pressing individual cable wires down into connections at the back of a patch panel",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which features of a cable would an advanced cable tester be able to determine that a basic tester could not?",
              "answer": "attenuation interference & resistance",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In which scenario would you be most likely to use a tone generator/probe?",
              "answer": "Determining the termination point of a cable run",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A Wi-Fi analyzer can be used to determine which properties of wireless signals?",
              "answer":
                  "Optimal channel use. signal strength and how often transmission errors are encountered",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In which scenario would you be most likely to use a loopback plug?",
              "answer":
                  "suspectedissues with your local network can you face port",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In which scenario would you be most likely to use a crimper?",
              "answer": "Attaching a connected to a cable end",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A multimeter can help to ascertain which properties of a cable?",
              "answer": "Resistance and continuity",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In which scenario would you be most likely to use a cable stripper?",
              "answer": "Preparing a cable for crimping",
            },
          ],
        },

        //Network types
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which characteristics of cable Internet service might be considered to be disadvantages?",
              "answer": "volume of users and living in a very remote area",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Hi speed Internet access over a digital subscriber line uses which type of carrier?",
              "answer": "Phone lines",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A wireless mesh network would be likely be configured for which type of access?",
              "answer": "802.11",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What would be considered to be the primary benefit of implementing a WAN for your business?",
              "answer":
                  "Interconnecting all your locations to be able to share resources",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which connection methods would you most likely implement for devices in a PAN?",
              "answer": "Wi-Fi and Bluetooth",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of ISDN service would offer the highest bandwidth?",
              "answer": "E1-PRI",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which cellular network access method is based on a unique device identifying value?",
              "answer": "CDMA",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of entity would be most likely to implement a MAN?",
              "answer": "A university",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What would be considered to be the primary benefit of satellite Internet access?",
              "answer": "Able to reach very remote areas",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In which type of environment would you most likely encounter a SOHO LAN?",
              "answer": "A small business",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is meant by the description of fiber optic as being a converged service?",
              "answer": "It can carry voice video and data on the same cable",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The area where obstacles may interfere with line of sight wireless service is known as what zone?",
              "answer": "Fresnel Wireless network protocols",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which channels are typically considered to be good candidates for a Wi-Fi device operating in a 2.4 GHZ band?",
              "answer": "1,6,&11",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which cellular service generation first introduced support for mobile Internet access and features such as video calling?",
              "answer": "3G",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Zigbee and Z-wave most likely to be found in which type of Implementation?",
              "answer": "A smart home",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which general statement correctly differentiates between the 2.4 & t GHzfrequency bands?",
              "answer": "2.4 is generally able to carry further than 5 GHz",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "802.11n offered improvements over earlier Wi-Fi implementations by primarily adding which features?",
              "answer": "Increased signal intensity & more antn",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which capability was introduced by 802.11 AC set no other previous Wi-Fi standard could offer?",
              "answer": "Using dual band signaling",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which maximum bandwidth with speed was available when using 802.11g?",
              "answer": "54 Mbps",
            },
            {
              "question": "Over which frequency does 802.11 a operate?",
              "answer": "5GHz",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which application would be best suited to using near field communication (NFC)?",
              "answer": "A pymnt methd",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is a common connection issue with 802.11b that is not a prevalent with 802.11a?",
              "answer": "Interference",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The 2.4 GHZ band is divided up into how many channels when using Bluetooth devices?",
              "answer": "79 Configuring a wide/wireless network",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which quality of service component is described as resulting from variation of delays in a packet stream?",
              "answer": "jitter",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which wireless encryption method would be considered to be better than no security but notparticularly secure by today’s standards?",
              "answer": "WEP",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements describe disadvantages of cable modem service that were not an issue with DSL service?",
              "answer":
                  "Cable modems use shared bandwidth and did not always offer the speeds advertised. cable modem users may have been on same LAN, DSL users werent",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Configuring A NIC to receive an IP address automatically informs the system to use which network service?",
              "answer": "DHCP",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A small office home office (SOHO) network router that includes data ports for which switching is known as which device?",
              "answer": "Layer 3 switch",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A client request for service over a particular port that creates a temporary rule to allow that port to remain open for return traffic is known as what process in a firewall?",
              "answer": "Port triggering",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements best describes the characteristics of an IP address?",
              "answer":
                  "He has two sections indicating the host address and the network address. it is logical address that can be changed",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In the user devices such a smart phones and tablets will typically connect to SOHO network in which manner?",
              "answer": "Wi-Fi",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which devices would be best categorized as LOT devices?",
              "answer": "Thermostat and security system",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which access point configuration setting is also known as the network name?",
              "answer": "SSID",
            },
          ],
        },

        //Networking
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which characteristics of a cable modem distinguish it from other modems?",
              "answer": "Always on & use cable TV lines",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement best describes the differencebetween a hub and a bridge?",
              "answer":
                  "Hubs come in active and passive varieties bridges do not. hubs operate at Layer 1 of the OSI model bridges operate At layer 2 hubs send incoming data over all other ports, bridges do not",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which terms used 2 describe a disguised system that appears 2 be of interest or value 2 lure an attacker?",
              "answer": "Honeypot",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which scenario would equate a full duplex transmission?",
              "answer": "2 people arguing with each other",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A patch panel can best be thought of in which manner?",
              "answer":
                  "A centralized termination point for extensions of network cables",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement best describe the characteristics of a router?",
              "answer":
                  "They isolate networks from each other & don’t forget broadcast packets. Operate at layer 3 of the OS I model. they connect multiple networks together",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which option describes the process of devices such as Wi-Fi access points reporting their usage & status info to a cloud-based management point?",
              "answer": "Backhaul",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which characteristics of a switch can be advantageous to network at deployment?",
              "answer":
                  "They increase network performance by reducing collision and they improve network performance by regulating the flow of traffic",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Ethernet over power can sometimes be used as an altern to which networking implementation?",
              "answer": "Wi-Fi",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which devices would most likely require (PoE)?",
              "answer": "Wi-Fi access point and a security camera",
            },
          ],
        },

        //Implementing network concepts
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Network address translation serves which purpose in LAN environment?",
              "answer":
                  "Converting internal private IP addresses to external public addresses",
            },
            {
              "question": "VLAN trunking implemented in which scenario?",
              "answer": "Single VLAN exists on multiple switches",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of VPN configuration does not require any client software or manually initiated connections from client systems?",
              "answer": "Site to site",
            },
            {
              "question": "Sequencial steps of the DHCP process.",
              "answer": "Discover, Offer, Request, Acknowledgement , and Lease",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which subnet mask would you most likely find in use if your IP address was 192.168.1.100?",
              "answer": "255.255.255.0",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "When client system opens a browser & enters www.scom in address bar which processes will be performed by the local DNS server?",
              "answer": "Forward lookup & caching",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which decimal value critically translates the binary value of 10101000?",
              "answer": "168",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "If you discover that a client system has an IP address of 169.254.25.35 what might you be able to determine about the state of your network?",
              "answer":
                  "some client systems are not able to contact a DHCP server",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In which scenario might you find asystem with no default gateway?",
              "answer": "A client on an isolated network such as a lab",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which decimal/binary combination is represented by letter F in hexadecimal?",
              "answer": "15/1111",
            },
          ],
        },

        //TCP and UDP ports
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question": "Which options are components of the SLP protocol?",
              "answer": "User agents and service agents",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which application uses port 3389 by default?",
              "answer": "A remote desktop connection",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which port is used by SSH by default?",
              "answer": "22",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Traffic originating over ports 161 and 162 would indicate which type of operation?",
              "answer": "Monitoring a network device",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "If a website is requested over port 443 which prefix would you expect to see in the address bar of your browser?",
              "answer": "HTTPS",
            },
            {
              "question": "Over which port would an outgoing email be sent?",
              "answer": "25",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Lightweight directory access protocol uses which port by default?",
              "answer": "389",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Request over port 445 could be described as using which protocols?",
              "answer": "CIFS and SMB",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The NetBIOS protocol would be best suited to which type of request?",
              "answer": "Searching for a file on FileServer 1",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements best describe the characteristics of the TCP protocol?",
              "answer": "It is reliable and it uses acknowledgments",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Request originating from port 548 would most likely be coming from which system?",
              "answer": "A MAC client",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which option would you be asking for if the request was sent out over port 53?",
              "answer": "A name to IP address mapping",
            },
          ],
        },

        //Network Hosts
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which networking task would best describe the process of authentication?",
              "answer": "Supplying a username and password",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which option would be the closest analogy to the DNS servers?",
              "answer": "A phone book",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the primary benefit of implementing a DHCP server on a network?",
              "answer":
                  "Client systems can obtain an IP address configuration automatically",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement accurately describe the circumstances of when it would be appropriate to use a dedicated file server?",
              "answer":
                  "When you require a fast access to the network attached storage. And when security is a concern and client should authenticate",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which networking benefit can be provided by implementing a proxy server?",
              "answer":
                  "Filtering of web content and increase speed for web content",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A legacy system is often maintained in a networking moment for which reasons?",
              "answer":
                  "It provides a unique or special service and it maintains backward compatibility",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which mail protocol is responsible only for sending mail?",
              "answer": "smtp",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which network device would be able to proactively stop it intrusion into your network?",
              "answer": "IPS",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which device or system would most likely not support using Syslog by default?",
              "answer": "A window server",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A Web server delivers content to clients using which protocol?",
              "answer": "Http",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following would you consider to be a downside of using a print server?",
              "answer":
                  "Multi function printer considerations and printing job status considerations",
            },
          ],
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      "category": "A+ 1002",
      "items": [
        // A Study
        "Comparing Common Operating Systems",
        "Microsoft operating System Installation & Upgrade",
        "Microsoft command line tools",
        "MS Operating System Administrative Tools",
        "Windows control panel Utilities",
        "Application Installation, Networking, & tools",
        "Security Fundamentals",
        "Critical security concepts",
        "Software Troubleshooting",
        "Operational procedures best practices",
        "System Utilities",
      ],
      "questions": [
        /**************************************
     *    A_ study guid.pdf
    **************************************/
        // Comparing Common Operating Systems
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which version of windows introduced Bit locker to go?",
              "answer": "Windows 7",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following do you make available first so that your network- based automated deployment can proceed with exclusive access to the installation volume?",
              "answer": "Boot. Wim",
            },
            {
              "question": "Where don users find additional Windows 10 themes?",
              "answer": "Windows store.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What applet in Settings will let you recover a failed installation?",
              "answer": "Update and Security",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What OS would you choose if you required 64-bit processing, a user- friendly GUI, support for an encrypted file system, and a command line interface?",
              "answer": "Windows",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following is an open source phone/tablet OS?",
              "answer": "Android",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the effective upper limit for RAM in 32-bit processing?",
              "answer": "4GB",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which version of windows introduced Bitlocker in the Professional edition?",
              "answer": "Windows 8",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following should contain the unpacked installation binaries to support an automated network-based rollout of your new OS?",
              "answer": "Network Share.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What OS would you choose if you wanted full access to the kernel and source code, were not concerned about security, and had no budget?",
              "answer": "FreeBSD",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following are you most likely to use for a one-off, manual installation of windows 10 on a machine with no CD/DVD access or network deployment solution?",
              "answer": "USB",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Microsoft operating System Installation & Upgrade
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following is a requirement for windows 10x64?",
              "answer": "2GB RAM",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following actions would you take to make drivers available to an automated installation of windows 10?",
              "answer": "Edit the unattend.xml file.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which settings app configures the Active Hours to prevent forced reboots when users are logged on?",
              "answer": "Update and Security.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which settings app configures time, date, region, and language settings?",
              "answer": "Time and Language settings.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The steps typically used for applications in a Windows 10 upgrade readiness plan are:",
              "answer":
                  "a) Identify important apps and assign importance levels to prioritize your applications.\nb) Identify and resolve problems with applications.\nc) Start the upgrade process.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "How many primary partitions are supported on GPT disks?",
              "answer": "128.",
            },
            {
              "question": "What should you download 3 rd party drivers from?",
              "answer": "Manufacturer’s website.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which configuration would you choose if you managed an office of less than ten users?",
              "answer": "Workgroup.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What do all the upgrade advisors check and report on?",
              "answer": "Drivers and Accounts.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following are storage spaces configuration?",
              "answer": "Mirror, Simple, and Parity.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following actions would let recover from a system failure with the least administrative effort?",
              "answer": "Restore a snapchat.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the volume containing the boot configuration database called?",
              "answer": "System volume.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Microsoft command line tools
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which command do you run to create a local user account?",
              "answer": "Net User.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following would you use after rejoining a client machine that had lost its trust relationship to the domain?",
              "answer": "gpupdate /force.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following command line tools would you run to script the copy of all files (including hidden and system) from one directory to another?",
              "answer": "XCopy.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following commands will map the network drive x; to the share “DATA” on the fileserver “SRV01” each time someone logs into the machine, but using the currently logged on user’s credentials?",
              "answer": "Net use x: //SRV01/data?persistent:yes /savecred",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following tools would you use to determine service dependencies?",
              "answer": "Services.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following commands will mount the wim file E:/wims/install.wim to the mount directory E:/mount?",
              "answer":
                  "dism /mount-wim/wimfile: E:/wims/install.wim /index 2 /mountdir: E:/mount",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which commands can run from the command line to navigate to the root form C:/program files (x86)/microsoft office/ packagemanifests and list the directories and files on the root drive?",
              "answer": "Cd/. then run dir",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following tools do you use on windows 10 machine when the Microsoft guidance directs you to edit a registry key?",
              "answer": "Regedit.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following commands would you run to check and fix protected operating system files?",
              "answer": "Sfc.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following can you use to strip all the formatting away from data to make it nearly universally portable?",
              "answer": "Notepad.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following commands would you use to determine if a client’s IP address is statically or DHCP assigned?",
              "answer": "Ipconfig",
            },
          ],
        },
        // MS Operating System Administrative Tools
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following utilities would you use to shrink and existing drive partition?",
              "answer": "Disk Manager.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following utilities would you use to kill an unresponsive application?",
              "answer": "Task Manager.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following utilities would you use to quickly determine the non-windows applications configured to launch automatically at start-up?",
              "answer": "MSConfig.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "You want to ensure that a particular application can always connect to the client in order to push update the latest application data regardless of the network the client is connected to. What do you do?",
              "answer":
                  "Enable for all profiles, Create an inbound firewall rule.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following actions would you take to minimize administrative overhead if you were responsible for managing just DHCP and DNS on a windows server on your network?",
              "answer":
                  "Create a custom mmc with only the DHCP and DNS snap ins.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What must you plan for when running windows Memory diagnostics that is not a concern with most other administrative tools?",
              "answer": "Machine downtime.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What tool would you use to set a password policy for the client machine’s local user accounts?",
              "answer": "Local Security Policy.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following tools would you use to create a baseline of system performance?",
              "answer": "Performance Monitor.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "After installing a new application, the machine performs slowly and frequently blue screens. The product documentation does not address this issue. What tool would you use to check for setup errors and messages?",
              "answer": "Event Viewer.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What tool would you use to make a flat file database available to an application you are developing?",
              "answer": "ODBC Data services.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following tools would you use to reset a local account password?",
              "answer": "Local users and groups.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What tool would you use to restart a stopped instance of the SQL service?",
              "answer": "Services.msc",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What tool would you use to share a printer with least administrative effort?",
              "answer": "Print management.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Windows control panel Utilities
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which Firewall network profile is automatically enforced with no user intervention?",
              "answer": "Domain.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following would let you change the screen resolution with least administrative effort?",
              "answer": "Right-click Desktop->Display settings.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following tabs would you select in File Explorer-> Options to disable Quick Access?",
              "answer": "General.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following choices would you type into the start menu search to configure virtual memory with the least administrative effort?",
              "answer": "Advanced System Settings.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which selection from the power options navigation menu would you choose to make the Hibernate available in Windows 10, assuming compatible hardware?",
              "answer": "Choose what the power buttons do.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following tabs would you access in internet options in order to manage add-ons?",
              "answer": "Programs.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Application Installation, Networking, & tools
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following network connections should always require data encryption?",
              "answer": "Wireless, VPN, WWAN.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following describes a NIC card that can utilize 100% of its available upstream and downstream bandwidth simultaneously?",
              "answer": "Full duplex.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What setup configuration would you choose for a new Windows 10 computer installed on your new home network which does not include a server?",
              "answer": "Workgroup.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What happens when you combine both share and NFTS permissions on a share?",
              "answer": "They combine to give the most restrictive permission.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What permissions must be assigned to the authenticated users group on the distribution share to ensure all users will have the application installed?",
              "answer": "Read, read and execute.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which disk management function is available in the MAC disk utility but not in the Microsoft disk management tools?",
              "answer": "Overwrite.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which commands would you likely run if there was a process you wanted to terminate?",
              "answer": "Ps, Kill.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following is the MAC password management tool?",
              "answer": "Keychain.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What must you know in order to allow an app through the windows defender firewall?",
              "answer": "The path to the executable.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which of the following is included with MAC OS X?",
              "answer": "Time Machine.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following acts as a firewall and web filter, provides shared network connections, and caches data to speed up common requests?",
              "answer": "Proxy.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Security Fundamentals
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "In order to ensure maximum security for your corporate owned mobile devices, which of the following should you make certain the device supports before you make your buying decisions?",
              "answer": "Remote wipe, Lockout policies, your MDM policies.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following record types must you add to DNS to implement DNSSEC?",
              "answer": "DNSKEY, RRSIG.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "When disposing of hardware storage devices, which of the following may you be required to obtain to ensure regulatory compliance for data security?",
              "answer": "Certificate of Destruction.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following would you install to redress issues of laptops disappearing?",
              "answer": "Cable locks.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following are examples of authentication possession (something you have) to support multifactor authentication?",
              "answer": "Key fob, Smart card.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following actions should you take before repurposing a hard disk?",
              "answer": "Perform low level format.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following should you install to support wireless authentication and network access?",
              "answer": "RADIUS server.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following best describes the principle of least privilege?",
              "answer":
                  "Assign users the least permission level required to do their jobs.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following best describes the function of organizational units?",
              "answer": "To organize like managed objects in the directory.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following best describes the kind of malware that infected the CFO’s laptop after he downloaded and installed a popular file sharing app?",
              "answer": "Trojan.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following best describes the activity of an intruder on the network who has changed the MAC address of their laptop to gain access to a network with MAC filtering enabled?",
              "answer": "Spoofing.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following are examples of inheritance possession (something you are) to support multifactor authentication?",
              "answer": "Retinal scanner, Fingerprint reader.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which wireless security solution should you choose?",
              "answer": "WPA2 (AES).",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Critical security concepts
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the name of a Microsoft windows feature that allows for user-based file level encryption?",
              "answer": "New technology file system (NTFS)",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What should you do to secure the built-in admin and guest accounts on any windows machine?",
              "answer": "Rename them.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following is a best practice in combating hackers?",
              "answer": "Disable autorun.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What would you call an authentication solution that enables a user to access multiple systems (such as your network and a cloud-based service) with your network login, despite the second service normally needing a separate username/password?",
              "answer": "Single sign-on (SSO).",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following encryption protocols are recommended for the small office home office (SOHO)?",
              "answer": "WPA2/AES.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following machines is best suited to have a BIOS/UEFI password for security?",
              "answer": "Campus computer lab.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following is the correct PowerShell cmdlet to create a user object in Active Directory?",
              "answer": "New-AdUser.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What happens when you move a file structure from the fileserver’s D: drive to E:?",
              "answer":
                  "File attributes (including security) are inherited from the new parent directory.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What would you call an attack that used many devices to simultaneously make requests of your cloud services, overwhelming them to the point where no one gets a response?",
              "answer": "DDos.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is your effective permission to a share (accessed across the network) to which you have been assigned Read share permissions and NTFS Modify permissions to?",
              "answer": "Read.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which toolset lets you restore a deleted active directory object?",
              "answer": "Active Directory Administrative Center.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the name of a Microsoft windows feature that allows for full volume encryption?",
              "answer": "Bitlocker.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What term best describes an attack that involves sending an email addressed to everyone in your company, that appears to come for an internal address and requires your network credentials in order to open an attachment, all in attempt to steal the credentials?",
              "answer": "Spear Phishing.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Software Troubleshooting
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "The steps for remediating a malware infected system in the correct order:",
              "answer":
                  "a) Identify and research malware symptoms.\nb) Quarantine the infected systems\nc) Disable system restore (in windows)\nc) Remediate the infected systems\nd) Schedule scans and run updates\ne) Enable system restore and create a restore point (windows).",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which tool would you use to boot Windows following a stop error from which the machine is unable to restart?",
              "answer": "WinPE.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The steps in the troubleshooting process in correct order:",
              "answer":
                  "a) Identify the problem\nb) Establish a theory of probable cause\nc) Test the theory to determine cause\nd) Establish a plan of action to resolve the problem and implement the solution\ne) Verify full system functionality and, if applicable, implement preventive measures\nf) Document findings, actions, and outcomes.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following actions would be appropriate responses to an “invalid boot disk” error message in windows?",
              "answer":
                  "Remove USB, verify boot order in SYSTEM BIOS, Remove CD/DVD.",
            },
            {
              "question": "What is a Windows stop error commonly called?",
              "answer": "BSoD",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What can a shutdown and restart of your windows 10 mobile device also be called?",
              "answer": "Soft reset.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following actions are you most likely to take in the event your mobile device has suffered unauthorized access via malware?",
              "answer":
                  "Change your password, restore from cloud backup, reinstall apps, Uninstall app.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What key do you strike before the windows logo screen appears to enter the Advanced Boot Options menu?",
              "answer": "F8",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Operational procedures best practices
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following protect you from electrostatic discharge (ESD)?",
              "answer": "Antistatic wrist strap, Ground mat, antistatic bag.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of these options is the most appropriate handling of a customer’s password when troubleshooting requires it?",
              "answer": "Ask user to type in the password themselves.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following is responsible for ensuring the integrity of the data (arrives unchanged) as it traverses the public internet?",
              "answer": "Hash algorithm.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Following a network compromise, which of these terms describes your record of who was in possession of evidence at a particular time?",
              "answer": "Chain of custody.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which two password policy settings combine to make it impossible for users to quickly reuse their last password?",
              "answer": "Enforce history, Minimum Age.",
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the last step in troubleshooting theory?",
              "answer": "Document findings, actions, and outcomes.",
            },
            {
              "question": "What is a “brownout”?",
              "answer": "Short-lived drop in voltage.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "When users are found in possession of content restricted by your Acceptable Use and corporate compliance policies, which of the following should be part of your first response?",
              "answer":
                  "Data/device preservation, reporting through proper channels, Problem identification.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "You have a script that needs to be edited with input values, but when you open the script you note there are several lines of text each preceded with “#”, indicating these lines are which of the following?",
              "answer": "Comments.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following are examples of proper communication and professional skills while dealing with a difficult customer?",
              "answer":
                  "Narrow the scope of the problem, clarify customer statements.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which configuration setup would you choose when implementing BranchCache in a remote office with no onsite server?",
              "answer": "Distributed.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following correctly identifies a document describing procedures for safe handling, use, storage, and disposal of potentially hazardous material’s?",
              "answer": "Material safety data sheet (MSDS).",
            },
          ],
        },
        // System Utilities
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "A user has reported they accidentally sent multiple print jobs to the wrong printer. Where do you go to purge the queue?",
              "answer": "Control panel -> Devices and Printers.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "You have determined that a block-level file corruption on the disk has damaged the driver files for a critical piece of hardware. The steps to fix it are:",
              "answer":
                  "Uninstall the device, scan for hardware changes, identify the correct drivers, update the drivers.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Where are windows features enabled and disabled in the windows 10GUI?",
              "answer": "Control panel -> Programs and Features",
            },
            {
              "question": "What’s new in Homegroup in windows 10?",
              "answer": "Homegroups are deprecated in Windows 10.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What must your do first as a prerequisite to establish a sync partnership?",
              "answer": "Enable offline folders.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Your DHCP server is acting up. Every time it does, clients fail to renew their IPs and can no longer communicate on the network when this happens, you notice every affected machine has an IP address in the 169 254 0 0/16. You open the Control Panel -> Network and sharing -> Adapter properties -> TCP/IP properties. From there, where will you navigate to in order to correct the issue?",
              "answer": "Alternative configuration.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the primary security concern around credential manager?",
              "answer": "It allows passwords to be displayed.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following features od bitlocker in unavailable without a TPM 2.0 module?",
              "answer": "Secure Boot (preboot security).",
            },
          ],
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Project Management",
      "items": [
        // Project Management
        "Project Documents",
        "Project Planning documents",
        "Project management practical exercises",
        "Quality and Procurement Planning",
        "Planning and controlling the project schedule",
        "Controlling project work and closing",
        "Communications, changes, and documentation",
        "Resource and Risk planning",
        "Scope, schedule and cost planning",
        "Project selection and Initiation",
      ],
      "questions": [
        /**************************************
     *   Proj Management study guide.pdf
    **************************************/
        // Project Documents
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which option is raw, uninterpreted data that includes the attributes of a deliverable?",
              "answer": " Work performance data",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Performance can be compared and evaluated against which measurable goal?",
              "answer": "Key performance Indicator (KPI)",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which procurement document is issued by a buyer to prospective sellers in which the buyer invites the sellers to submit proposals for completing specified work?",
              "answer": "Request for Proposal (RFP)",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which hierarchical chart is organized by function and accountabilities?",
              "answer": "Organizational Breakdown Structure (OBS)",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is used in the cycle between quality assurance and quality control to answer the question, “Are we measuring the right things”?",
              "answer": "Quality control measurements",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which document summarizes an agreement between parties before the agreement or contract is formally signed?",
              "answer": "Letter of Intent (LOI)",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which document is used to track requests to change project processes,, baselines, or documents?",
              "answer": "Change request form",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the difference between what a project has earned to date and what it has cost?",
              "answer": "Cost Variance (SV)",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which is a dependency relationship in which one activity must finish before another activity can finish?",
              "answer": "Finish to Finish (FF)",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Project Planning documents
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which documents includes the names, contact information, positions, and roles for individuals who may affect or be affected by the project?",
              "answer": "Stakeholder register.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A RACI matrix is an example of which type of resource planning document?",
              "answer": "Project staff assignments.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following is an element of the Project Management Plan?",
              "answer": "Subsidiary management plans.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which document provides high level information about the project, such as the project purpose, budget, schedule, and assumptions?",
              "answer": "Charter",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which vendor solicitation document is used to solicit information about the capabilities of prospective sellers?",
              "answer": "Request for information (RFI)",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which one of the following documents provide credibility to your activity cost estimates?",
              "answer": "Basis of estimates.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following are significant points in the WBS that signify the start or end of a sub- deliverable, or phase?",
              "answer": "Milestones",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following contains information and details about work packages?",
              "answer": "WBS",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which planning document includes the description or each risk, its potential impact, and its root causes?",
              "answer": "Risk register",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Project management practical exercises
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Your EAC formula includes the SPI. What can you assume this means?",
              "answer": "Your deadline is firm.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Your project has a \$1 million budget and a one-year time frame. After 3 months you have completed 20% of the work. What is the earned value?",
              "answer": "\$200,000",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Your project has an SPI of .90 and a CPI of 1.0. What does this indicate about your project performance?",
              "answer": "The project is behind schedule and on budget",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Your project has an SPI of 1.2 and a CPI of .80. what does this indicate about your project performance?",
              "answer": "The project is ahead of schedule and over budget.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Your project has a CPI of.92 and you expect this rate of spending to continue. If your original budget was \$1 million, what is your new Estimate at completion (EAC)?",
              "answer": "1,086,957",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "You were working on a project team with 5 members. Three additional members have been added. How many more communication channels are there now?",
              "answer": "18",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The cost to build your own network firewall is \$10,000 plus \$100 daily maintenance. The cost to outsource this is \$5,000 plus \$200 daily maintenance. What is the break-even point, when the cost to build your own firewall equals the cost to outsource?",
              "answer": "Day 50",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Your project has \$1 million budget and a one-year time frame. After 6 months you have completed 60% of the work and you have spent \$70,000. What is the cost value?",
              "answer": "-\$100,000",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In the following control chart exercise, the upper control limit is 10 and the lower control limit is 2. Which of the following data series indicates the process is out of control:",
              "answer": "2,9,8,7,8,9,10,8,5,9",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "You have an earned value of \$500,000 and a planned value of \$550,000. What is the schedule performance index?.",
              "answer": "91",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Quality and Procurement Planning
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of costs are incurred before the product or service is released to the customer, and includes rework or scrap?",
              "answer": "Internal failure",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which action is an example of a quality assurance activity?",
              "answer": "Following documented processes.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of contract stipulates a fixed price and includes an additional motivation or bonus- for early completion or some other measure of good performance?",
              "answer": "Fixed price plus incentive fee (FPIF)",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which action is an example of a Quality Control activity?",
              "answer": "Inspecting deliverables",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "During a car decision, a customer must decide between a car with all of the latest features and technology, and a car without any upgrades. Which word best describes the difference between these two vehicles?",
              "answer": "Grade",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Preventive actions, corrective actions, and defect repairs are all reasons to create which type of document?",
              "answer": "Change request",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of waste involves unnecessary movement of goods or moving goods to different areas to complete tasks?",
              "answer": "Transportation",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which quality tool can be used to identify the root cause of a defect found during quality control inspections?",
              "answer": "Ishikawa diagram",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of contract includes the seller’s real costs, plus a fixed fee or a fixed percentage of costs, which represents the seller’s profit?",
              "answer": "Cost plus fixed Fee (CPFF)",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Planning and controlling the project schedule
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "You are performing a forward pass through your project schedule. Activity G is the predecessor of activity H. If the early finish of activity G is 3, what is the early start of activity H?",
              "answer": "4",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "An activity on the critical path is running late. Your cost performance has been excellent and you have excess funds. How can you best protect the critical activity?",
              "answer":
                  "Add more resources to the activity to shorten its duration.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which path would be the critical path in a project schedule?",
              "answer": "A-b-c-d-e-f = 12",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Activity H. Activity H. has several months of float. What is the best action to take?",
              "answer":
                  "Employ resource smoothing by using the float to delay the start of Activity H by one month.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Activity H is a predecessor to activity E. If activity 5 can be delayed up to 5 months without delaying the start of Activity E, what is the free float of activity H?",
              "answer": "5",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Activities B, C and D have the predecessor A. What does this mean?",
              "answer": "Activity A diverges into three paths.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "You are performing a backward pass through your project schedule. Activity J is the successor of activity I. If the late start of activity J is 6, what is the late finish of activity I?",
              "answer": "5",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Activity E, on the critical path, is running late You have no extra money, and the money, and the subsequent (and final) project activity has a discretionary dependency on Activity E. What should you do?",
              "answer":
                  "Perform the activity at the same time as its successor activity, to make up time.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "An activity on the critical path is running late, you have similarly skilled employees working on a non-critical activity. You are slightly over budget. How can you best protect the critical activity?",
              "answer":
                  "Move resources away form the non-critical activity to protect the activity on the critical path.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Activity D has the following key dates: early start is 5, late start is 7, early finish is 9, and late finish is 11. What is the float on activity D?",
              "answer": "2",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Controlling project work and closing
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "How can you use earned value management formulas in schedule performance review?",
              "answer":
                  "If earned and planned values are equal, you know the project is on schedule. If you have SPI values of greater than 1, the project is ahead of schedule.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which aspects of budget forecasting using earned value formulas and indexes are correct?",
              "answer":
                  "Formula for EAC= BAC/CPI. Formula for EAC=ETC + AC. EAC predicts the total project cost based on current performance. ETC estimates amount of cost required for remaining work.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which document provides the basis for measuring and reporting schedule performance?",
              "answer": "Schedule baseline",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "You are trying to determine how your project is performing in terms of cost. You have an actual cost of \$5,000 and your planned value for this stage of completion was \$4,250. Your earned value calculates to be \$4,000. What would your cost performance index be?",
              "answer": "0.80",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "When using lessons in a formative evaluation, what type of actions would you take?",
              "answer":
                  "Apply results to future strategic planning. Perform modification to improve performance.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "When closing a project or phase, which important activity involves meeting with the the project stakeholders?",
              "answer": "Acceptance of deliverables.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which are the key roles defined in scrum methodology?",
              "answer": "Product owner, developmental team, scrum master.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Communications, changes, and documentation
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Select the correct order of events in a communication model.",
              "answer":
                  "Encode. Transmit message. Decode. Acknowledge. Feedback message",
            },
            {
              "question": "Select the correct order of change control events.",
              "answer":
                  "Submit change request. Evaluate the impact. Explore the alternatives. Obtain approval.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Select the examples of constraints to project success.",
              "answer":
                  "The budget is cut by 20%. There are delays in mandatory inspections. A key stakeholder wants to add a new feature.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Select the items that are part of the cope, schedule, and/or cost baselines.",
              "answer":
                  "The budget at completion is \$1,000,000. The actual costs should be \$100,000 after six months. The product will include 5 value-added customer requirements.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Identify the factors that influence communication methods.",
              "answer": "Time zones. Cross-cultural factors, language.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Select the type of common project changes.",
              "answer": "Risk. Scope. Rules an regulations. Budget.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Identify the events that trigger communication.",
              "answer": "Milestones. Project change. Schedule changes",
            },
            {
              "question": "Select the examples of vendor documents.",
              "answer": "Request for proposal. Invitation for bid.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Resource and Risk planning
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "The project manager’s authority and access to resources varies depending on the team organizational structure. Match the situation with the type of team organizational structure.",
              "answer":
                  "The project administrative staff is full time-projectized. Project manager has high level of access to resources- projectized. The functional manager controls the budget – functional. Project manager is part time-functional. There is a blend of organizational structures – Matrix. Project manager has a high level of authority – Projectized.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Select the types of organizational changes?",
              "answer":
                  "Internal reorganization, Merger/acquisition, Relocation.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Identify the attributes required required to successfully manage teams.",
              "answer": "Listening skills, Leadership, Group facilitation.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which strategies can be used to address risk?",
              "answer": "Mitigate, accept, transfer, avoid.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In a project to create a new user interface, Monica will do the actual programming of the user interface. Ganesh is the subject matter expert. Janice needs to be informed when the programming is complete. Brian must verify that the user interface meets customer requirements. Using a RACI assignment matrix match the employee with their role.",
              "answer":
                  "Ganesh- consult. Monica-responsible. Brian-accountable. Janice-inform.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which of these are paths of a SWOT analysis?",
              "answer": "Strengths, threats, weaknesses, opportunities.",
            }
          ],
        },
        // Scope, schedule and cost planning
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which are the common tools and techniques to gather project requirements?",
              "answer": "Questionnaires, facilitated workshops. Prototypes",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "When planning the project schedule, project activities and milestones are identified. Match each of the characteristics as being associated with an activity or a milestone.",
              "answer":
                  "The result of decomposing a work package – Activity. Trigger processes – Milestone. Decision point – Milestone. Can be mandatory or optional – Milestone. Can be estimated in terms of cost and time – activity.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which are the components of a project scope statement?",
              "answer":
                  "Project assumptions. Product scope description. Product acceptance criteria. Project exclusions.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following statement best defines the work breakdown structure?",
              "answer":
                  "A hierarchical chart that shows the decomposition of work into progressively smaller components.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The durations of activities A, B, C, D, E, F, and G are 1,2,7,4,5, 2, and 4 respectively. Which of the following option would be the critical path?",
              "answer": "A-C-F-G.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which are the estimation techniques that can be used to determine activity durations?",
              "answer":
                  "Parametric estimating, Analogous estimating, Three-point estimating",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following considerations should be made when allocating resources to the project activities?",
              "answer":
                  "Quantity of resources required. Required skill sets. Types of resources. Project team roles.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Project selection and Initiation
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question": "Which characteristics uniquely define a project?",
              "answer":
                  "Project purpose aligns with specific strategic business goals. Produces a unique product, service, or result, project work lasts a specific, temporary duration.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Identity key personal competencies to look for in a project manager.",
              "answer":
                  "Ability to motivate team members. Responsive to unexpected changes.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which are the common methods to classify stakeholders when performing a stakeholder analysis?",
              "answer": "Power. Interest. Impact. Influence.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Identify elements of project charter. Identifies the business need.",
              "answer":
                  "Contains approval requirements. Names the project manager.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which are the reasons that drive a business case for bringing about a project?",
              "answer":
                  "Technological advances. Market demand. Legal requirement. Customer request.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Identify the activities and processes that take place during the specific project stages.",
              "answer":
                  "In the executing stage, work to create the project deliverables is performed. Closing stage processes include documenting lessons learned and closing contacts. Quality assurance takes place during the monitoring & controlling stage. Obtaining authorization for a project takes place during the initiating stage.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Match the methodology characteristic with the corresponding type of project life cycle.",
              "answer":
                  "iterative cycles-adaptive. Rolling wave planning-adaptive. Sequential-predictive. Scope- adjustments-adaptive. Plan-driven-predictive.",
            },
          ],
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Security",
      "items": [
        // Security
        "The Present Threat Landscape",
        "Types of Malware",
        "Social Engineering and Related Attacks",
        "Application and service attacks",
        "Cryptographic and Wireless Attacks",
        "Penetration testing and vulnerability scanning",
        "Impacts from vulnerability types",
        "Components supporting organizational",
        "Security Assessment Using Software Tools",
        "Cryptography",
        "Public Key infrastructure",
        "Wireless Security Settings",
        "Analyzing output from security technologies",
        "Deploying Mobile devices securely",
        "Implementing secure protocols",
        "Trouble shooting common security issues",
        "Identity Concepts and Access Services",
        "Identity and Access management controls",
        "Common Account Management Practices",
        "Frameworks, Guidelines, and physical Security",
        "Implement Secure Network Architecture concepts",
        "Secure system and Application Design and Deployment",
        "Cloud, Virtualization, and Resiliency Concepts",
        "Policies, Plans, and Procedures",
        "Business Impact Analysis and Risk Management",
        "Incident response, Forensics, and Disaster Recovery",
      ],
      "questions": [
        /**************************************
     *   Security_study guide.pdf
    **************************************/
        // The Present Threat Landscape
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements describe a competitor as a potential threat actor?",
              "answer":
                  "They may perform espionage to teal intellectual property (IP). They can do sabotage to destroy stock value. They may deface web sites to ruin reputations and goodwill.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement regarding of compromise is not true?",
              "answer": "S/MIME is a popular loC tool.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which statements concerning Hacktivists is true?",
              "answer":
                  "Some associate with a particular country, government, entity, or cause, while others express no particular allegiance.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement best represents as potential internal structured threat?",
              "answer":
                  "Running Kali Linux from a USB flash drive on a corporate workstation.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements describe the characteristics of an advanced persistent threats (APT)?",
              "answer":
                  "They are unrelenting and focused, often with a long -term strategy. They are known for bleeding edge, stealth malware and zero-days. They often perform cost/benefit analysis before selecting targets.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the least likely motivator of a black-hat hacker in today’s cyber world?",
              "answer": "Notoriety",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement describe a threat actor or argent with sophistication, resources, and extensive funding to launch attacks?",
              "answer":
                  "The owner of malware-as-a-service cloud provider in the dark web. A member of a crime syndicate in Eastern Europe. A member of a well-established hacktivist group. A state sponsored employee of a rogue nation.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following are considered types of security controls commonly used to countermeasure attacks and threats?",
              "answer": "Managerial. Physical. Administrative. Technical.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What does the use of a program like Wireshark allow you to do?",
              "answer":
                  "Capture network packets. View details of malware code.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which terms would represent a potential unstructured internal threat or vulnerability?",
              "answer":
                  "Accidental and non-malicious. Poor security awareness training. No enforced AUP. Using unprovisioned USB drive brought from home.",
            },
            {
              "question": "What does TOR stand for?",
              "answer": "The onion Router.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which of the following are popular exploit kits?",
              "answer": "RIG EK. Sundown. Magnitude. Neutrino.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The security triad can help provide the adequate protection of network resources. Which of the following is not officially part of the security triad?",
              "answer": "Identity",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What term describes a person, method, operation, technique, or entity that has the potential to initiate, transport, carry out, or in any way support a particular exploit?",
              "answer": "Threat agent.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Types of Malware
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of event leads the logic bombs to trigger an exploit?",
              "answer":
                  "A number of times code executes. A particular date and time. On a popular holiday. Mouse movements.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "When searching the common vulnerabilities and exposures (CVE) list’s national vulnerability database (NVD), what scoring information is provided for each vulnerability?",
              "answer":
                  "Impact sub score. CVSS Base Score. Exploitability subscore.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Trojan horse malware masquerades as legitimate program. What are the common examples of trojan application?",
              "answer":
                  "Games. Freeware form P2P sites. Shareware utilities. Device drivers.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What term describes a seemingly benign JPEG picture that may actually contain destructive malware?",
              "answer": "Stegomalware.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What term describes the malware that bundles up different types of malicious code into a single package and delivers it in a email attachment?",
              "answer": "Polymorphic packer.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which one is not likely to be a common ransomware vector?",
              "answer": "Digitally signed upgrade.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which statement is false regarding keyloggers?",
              "answer":
                  "They can all evade special on-screen keyboard software.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which specific form of malicious software is often used to generate a convert channel so that the remote attacker can access and control the system even on phones and other mobile devices?",
              "answer": "Backdoor",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which is a specific form of malware, often part of multistage exploits, that is known for creating backdoors to C&C servers giving crackers access to a system?",
              "answer": "RAT",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of virus simultaneously attacks the boot sector and executable files so that it combines the characteristics of file infector and boot sector viruses?",
              "answer": "Multipartite.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What category of malware can actually be an entire operating system, smart device, gaming system, or even an automobile?",
              "answer": "Spyware",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "You are performing a vulnerability assessment at regional branch office for your company. Which specific type of malware often targets the BIOS, boot loader, kernel, or system files and is difficult to detect since it often initiates before the operating system has fully booted?",
              "answer": "Rootkit",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement is not true concerning malware worms?",
              "answer":
                  "A worm usually spreads with user actioWhat is it called when cryptomalware is delivered when a user innocently visits an infected web site and downloads and installs it without their knowledge?n and distributes throughout a single systems kernel, components, and processes.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is it called when cryptomalware is delivered when a user innocently visits an infected web site and downloads and installs it without their knowledge?",
              "answer": "Drive-by",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the function that bots and botnets do not perform?",
              "answer": "Corrupt routing tables.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Social Engineering and Related Attacks
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "It is quite common, especially in large organizations, to employ a security policy that prohibits one person entering a restricted area simultaneously using another’s access credentials. What is this type of social engineering called?",
              "answer": "Tailgating",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which one of the following is not a technique to mitigate against typo squatting?",
              "answer": "Typing directly into a browser address bar.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following attack is known for stealing information from point-of-state systems and credit card readers at gas stations, convenience stores. And kiosks?",
              "answer": "Shimming.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which technique is commonly performed to re-engineer classic attack code to create new malware variants and hybrids?",
              "answer": "Refactoring",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which term best describes targeting high level employees or senior management and directors with potentially malicious e-mail?",
              "answer": "Whaling",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "There are measurable reasons why e-mail and web-based attacks are so successful?",
              "answer":
                  "Which of the following would be valid causes? Suboptimal perimeter security. No written AUP. Lack of enforcement. Poor BYOD protection policy.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which one of the following protocols is least likely to be part of a session hijacking or spoofing attack?",
              "answer": "UDP",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following mechanisms could be used to perform shoulder surfing?",
              "answer": "Cell phone, telescope, smart glasses, Binoculars.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of attack, also known as UI redressing, uses transparent layers to trick uses into clicking on a button or link on another web page when they are actually trying to click on the top-level web page?",
              "answer": "Clickjacking.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of attack would most likely attempt to take advantage of text messages on an iPhone or iPad?",
              "answer": "Smishing",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following things would a cracker hope to find in a dumpster diving expedition?",
              "answer": "Invoices. Organizational charts. Calendars. Memos.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which one of the following terms is not another word for impersonation?",
              "answer": "Shimming",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "URL hijacking goes by many names in the security industry. Which one of the following is technically not another name for URL hijacking?",
              "answer": "Clickjacking.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Application and service attacks
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "What would not make a system vulnerable to a DNS poisoning attack?",
              "answer": "Not implementing BPDU guard.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which attack uses the same techniques as MITM except that a trojan horse is used to capture and manipulate calls between the web-based client and its security mechanisms on an ad hoc basis?",
              "answer": "Man-in-the-browser.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What common threat vector finds the attacker sending larger than expected input so that adjacent memory addresses are overwritten in order to execute a payload?",
              "answer": "Buffer overflow.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What type of attack would best characterize a small forged DNS request packet provoking a much larger reply form the victim systems?",
              "answer": "Amplification.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which common form of DDoS attack consists of a group of systems loaded with code that leverages a c2 server that remotely controls zombie computers often using and peer-to-peer?",
              "answer": "Botnet",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements are true regarding injection attacks?",
              "answer":
                  "This attack is often the result on MITM or RAT attack. They often insert false MAC or IP addresses. Exploit tools like Loki can be used.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which attack, also known as one-click attack,compromises a user’s browser and consequently send unauthorized commands to a web site which it trusts?",
              "answer": "Cross-site request forgery.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In which type of attack is encryption performed before authentication in order to facilitate rapid detection and rejection of bogus packets by the receiving device?",
              "answer": "Replay attack.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which is not one of the synonymous names with domain hijacking and URL hijacking?",
              "answer": "Tailgating",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What are the elements that attackers commonly spoof?",
              "answer":
                  "MAC addresses. law enforcement IDs. Domains and URLs., IPv4 and Ipv6 addresses. Peer routers.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement is false regarding ARP poisoning attacks?",
              "answer": "It is a very common attack on IPv4 and IPv6 networks.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which phase of an APT involves exploiting a flaw or a bug in a system design or access control configuration in order to gain root or administrative access?",
              "answer": "Privilege escalation.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What type of attack can specifically take advantage of windows safe mode?",
              "answer": "Pass the hash.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What represents a benign man-in-the-middle scenario?",
              "answer":
                  "NAT translation firewall. Encryption proxy server. Application layer getaway.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which term best describes an unpublished exploit that security software vendors and cloud security services are presently unaware of?",
              "answer": "Zero day.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Cryptographic and Wireless Attacks
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Using a tool like Cain, what are the options available when cracking protocol hashes?",
              "answer": "Dictionary attack, Brute-force attack.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement represents when two different inputs produce an identical output?",
              "answer": "Hash collision.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What technology is susceptible to data being stolen, skimmed, and scanned by anyone with easily obtained reader?",
              "answer": "RFID",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Malicious rogue access points attempt to take sensitive data like usernames, passwords and personally identifiable information (PII). What represents a category of this malicious attempt?",
              "answer": "Evil twin. Honeypot.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "According to statisticians, the probability that two people in a group of people share the same birthday is greater than 50 percent. What is the least number of people in the group that meet the requirements of this probability?",
              "answer": "23",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "WEP implements an initialization vector, which is a clear-text pseudo-random number used along with the secret key for data encryption. How many bits are in the original WEP IV?",
              "answer": "24",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which attack on mobile devices takes advantage of sending contact information automatically without authentication or authorization?",
              "answer": "Bluejacking",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which wireless feature was previously called Wi-Fi simple config?",
              "answer": "WPS",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which popular downgrade attack is a man-in-the-middle exploit that leverages internet and security software clients’ willingness to fallback to SSL 3.0?",
              "answer": "Poodle",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which is not an 802.11 management or control frame?",
              "answer": "Reassembly",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which are valid forms of cipher attacks?",
              "answer":
                  "Chosen-plaintext attack. Chosen-Ciphertext Attack. Known-plaintext Attack.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which statement is false concerning online attacks?",
              "answer":
                  "Online attacks commonly involve a parallel hash collision search brute-force attack.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What are the valid techniques for mitigating replay attacks?",
              "answer":
                  "Deploy secure cookies. Use nonces with communication. Randomize initial sequence number.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which statement is not true about jamming attacks?",
              "answer":
                  "Poorly written drivers on endpoint wireless NICs rarely demonstrate the characteristics of a jamming attack.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Penetration testing and vulnerability scanning
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Match the network security testing type with the characteristics.",
              "answer":
                  "Active-intrusive, inline-intrusive, Social Engineering-Nonintrusive, Packet Sniffing-Nonintrusive, promiscuous-non-intrusive, passive-nonintrusive.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which form of exploit allows you to jump from one segment or domain to another in order to deliver a payload?",
              "answer": "Pivot attack.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the alternate term used for piggybacking through a secured door?",
              "answer": "Tailgating.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "With respect to the identification of a lack of security controls in amn enterprise, which of the following is false?",
              "answer":
                  "It seldom involves comprehensive reporting or deep risk analysis.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following events best represents a false positive scenario?",
              "answer":
                  "An IPS alert and packet drop is triggered when an authorized end-user inputs the wrong complex password 5 times.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "When performing penetration testing the initial exploit will often involve which of the following activities?",
              "answer":
                  "Packet sniffing. Passive reconnaissance. Social engineering.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "After which one of the following system events would malicious code or scripts most likely not be persistent?",
              "answer": "AV scan.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Place the steps in the correct order to prepare for a penetration testing session in your accounting department?",
              "answer": "Enumerate. Learn. Explore. Adapt. Trial and error.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which one of the following is not a popular vulnerability scanning tool?",
              "answer": "Rig EK",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements are true with respect to the process of passively testing security controls?",
              "answer":
                  "Comprises scanning and snooping tools to gather information for analysis. Involves running security devices in Monitor Only mode. Most firewalls can use packet tracer capabilities.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following actions would most likely lead to common security misconfigurations at layer 2 of the OSI model?",
              "answer":
                  "Setting up port security on an access switch. Choosing an authentication mode on WAP. Designing a VLAN deployment.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following best represents an example of passive reconnaissance?",
              "answer": "Data mining social networks.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Match the application testing type with the characteristics?",
              "answer":
                  "No knowledge of internal working of the application-Black box. Can combine two other testing methods-gray box. Limited knowledge of fundamental aspects of the application-gray box. Tester knows structure, design, a dimple, implementation of application-white box, detailed study of complete structure of the code-white box. Design is not known to the tester-black box.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement concerning the pen testing and vulnerability scanning comparisons is false?",
              "answer":
                  "Vulnerability scanning is rarely automated and can take days to complete.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Impacts from vulnerability types
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which scenario is often related to synchronization errors in software code where malicious users can gain unauthorized access to a system or application?",
              "answer": "Race condition",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following may expose your organization or a user to exploits?",
              "answer":
                  "Hacktivism. Ransomware. Spear phishing. Poor database RBAC",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which tool serves as a memory scraper and a keystroke logger?",
              "answer": "poSeidon",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which technology tries to control to use, modification, and distribution of copyrighted software and multimedia content?",
              "answer": "DRM",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements are true regarding system misconfiguration?",
              "answer":
                  "Config files should be stored in a secure document library. Configurations should first be tested in virtual lab. Human error is the number one vulnerability.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement is not true regarding certificate and key management?",
              "answer": "Choose AAA or CRL over OCSP for revocation.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "During vulnerability scanning, you have discovered improper error handling on your intranet web servers where detailed internal error messages arebeing exposed to unauthorized users due improper input handling or error handling. Which statement would not be true in this scenario?",
              "answer": "SQL injection can be exposed,",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement is false concerning programs for training end users in security awareness?",
              "answer":
                  "The first step in the program is to motivate management.",
            },
            {
              "question": "What functions as an extension of IEEE 802 .1X?",
              "answer": "MACsec",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "At which site can you find the security policy project and the CIS critical security controls as a free resource?",
              "answer": "Sans.org",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement is true concerning resource exhaustion?",
              "answer": "It is an attack on availability.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "All architecture and design methodologies have weaknesses and vulnerabilities. Select if the statement is true or false.",
              "answer": "True",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which would not be considered a vulnerable business process?",
              "answer": "Using TLS and suite B instead of SSL and IKEv1",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Components supporting organizational
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "An encryption gateway cannot function on a single device between both an IPSec site-to-site VPN and a remote TLS VPN. Select if the statement is true or false.",
              "answer": "False",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which technology can translate and convert media streams between different technologies such as SSS7, 4G, LTE networks, and PBX systems?",
              "answer": "Media getaways.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which service can perform anti-spam, anti-virus, encryption, DLP, and more in your enterprise?",
              "answer": "Mail gateway.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which Cisco industry initiative controls access to enterprise resources and restricts the lateral movement of threats with micro segmentation?",
              "answer": "NAC",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which option is not a dynamic routing protocol?",
              "answer": "NAT",
            },
            {
              "question": "What are the characteristics of IPSec?",
              "answer":
                  "Operates in transport or tunnel mode. Provides for confidentiality and anti-replay services. Open framework that supports suite B and GET. Main protocols are ESP and AH.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the scenario called when there is illegal usage of bit torrents for downloading piratedsoftware into your corporate LAN, and the IPS sensor fails to alert you or block the traffic?",
              "answer": "False negative",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Wireless Access Points typically create wireless LANs at which layers of the OSI model?",
              "answer": "1 and 2",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which network service provides log collection, analysis, and forensics?",
              "answer": "SIEM",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which service can be integrated into web security and e-mail security solutions to scan e-mail, IM, SMS, and webmail for the presence of protected and sensitive corporate data?",
              "answer": "DLP",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which infrastructure device would most likely connect to a printer in the supply room at your office?",
              "answer": "Access switch",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which proxy service would best be used for PAT, business logic, and XML purposes in the enterprise?",
              "answer": "Translation proxy.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The cisco ASA 5585-X is a dominant security appliance in the specialty platform category. Select if the statement is true or false.",
              "answer": "True",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Security Assessment Using Software Tools
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Solid data backups are a key countermeasure to which type of malware attack?",
              "answer": "Ransomware",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What network tool is most likely to be used to examine ranges of Ip addresses, ports, and device locations presented in a customized graphical XML view with monitoring and management capabilities to detect, diagnose, and resolve network issues and outages?",
              "answer": "Network scanners.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Exploitation kills are used by penetration testers and crackers to find vulnerabilities and attack vectors. Which is not an exploit kit?",
              "answer": "OWASP Zap",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which is not a wireless scanner?",
              "answer": "Burp suite",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements accurately describe banner grabbing?",
              "answer":
                  "Malicious hackers can use it as part or reconnaissance attack. Hackers use it to server systems. The term “banner” usually refers to a message that a service sends when a host is first connecting. Default banners often reveal the type of software and version.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the practice of purposely, permanently, irretrievably removing or destroying the data stored on a data storage device?",
              "answer": "Data sanitization.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which compliance regulation is concerned with securing information in agencies of the federal government?",
              "answer": "FISMA",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Active scanners can act to autonomously fix security issues, such as blocking a potentially dangerous source IP prefix. Select if the statement is true or false.",
              "answer": "True",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What process embeds files or text messages within images and graphics so that no third party can detect the hidden data?",
              "answer": "Steganography.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "You are using the Cain password-cracking tool. Which is not a configuration tab in the main interface?",
              "answer": "MSSQL",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Automated vulnerability scanning tools can scan web applications and look for which of the following security vulnerabilities?",
              "answer":
                  "SQL injection. Cross-site scripting. Command injection. Path traversal.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements are true concerning protocol analyzers?",
              "answer":
                  "Advanced analyzers can generate statistics for trend analysis and network optimization. Traffic can be filtered and decoded to visualize what processes are occurring. They capture and analyze network traffic between two or more systems. They can be used to find network bottlenecks, troubleshoot, and analyze malware behavior.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which statement is false regarding honeypots?",
              "answer":
                  "It redirects attackers to valuable assets in order to trap them.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Cryptography
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of these are used when creating a digital signature?",
              "answer":
                  "A public/private key pair. The message that will be sent. A hashing algorithm. A signing algorithm.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which are the examples of stream ciphers?",
              "answer": "Scream, RC4",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements are true in relation to asymmetric algorithms?",
              "answer":
                  "A public key is shared with many people. Privacy is achieved when encrypting with a public key and decrypting with a private key. A private key is kept secret for a single person.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which of these are used when creating an HMAC?",
              "answer":
                  "A shared secret key. The message that will be sent. A hashing algorithm.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which statement correctly defines steganography?",
              "answer":
                  "It conceals information by hiding it in other information",
            },
            {
              "question": "What correctly defines non-reputation?",
              "answer":
                  "It ensures the original sender cannot deny sending data.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which statements correctly define a block cipher?",
              "answer":
                  "The key must be the same size as the data. They operate on fixed-size date.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "You are reviewing the properties of a secure cipher. Which statement best defines diffusion?",
              "answer":
                  "With each input but, half or more of the ciphertext bits should change.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What ensures that when a key is compromised, only a small set of messages are affected?",
              "answer": "Perfect forward secrecy",
            },
            {
              "question": "What are key stretching algorithms?",
              "answer": "PBKDF2. Bcrypt",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which asymmetric algorithm, is used for establishing a shared key?",
              "answer": "Diffie-Hellman",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "You want to ensure data has not been modified in transit. How can you accomplish this?",
              "answer":
                  "Use a hashing function on the data before sending to create a fingerprint and compare it to a fingerprint that is calculated upon reception.",
            },
            {
              "question": "What are the examples of substitution ciphers?",
              "answer": "vigenere, Caesar, ROT13.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which is the most secure method of exchanging secret keys?",
              "answer": "Asymmetric Algorithm.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which of these correctly describe AES?",
              "answer":
                  "It uses the Rijindael algorithm. It is classified as a symmetric algorithm. It is a block cipher.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is used at the network layer of the OSI model to encrypt data?",
              "answer": "IPsec",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is used to create a message digest that will be attached to data at rest or in transit?",
              "answer": "Hashing",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which hashing functions are not subject to a collision attack?",
              "answer": "SAHA-2. SHA-3",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which are true in relation to symmetric algorithms?",
              "answer":
                  "They are fast and used for bulk data encryption. The same secret key is used for encryption and decryption. The secret keys can be from 40 to 256 bits in length.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Public Key infrastructure
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which X.509 certificate format is used for exchanging keys?",
              "answer": "PKCS#12",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which describe the CA hierarchical trust model?",
              "answer":
                  "The root CA provides certificates to intermediate CAs. Intermediate Cas provide certificates to end users. The root CA can be online or offline.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which fields in a certificate are used to verify the chain of trust?",
              "answer": "Issued by. Issued to.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "You are requesting a certificate that will need to include your DNS names. Which certificate is the best to use in this case?",
              "answer": "SAN",
            },
            {
              "question": "What are the responsibilities of a CA?",
              "answer":
                  "Sign certificates. Store certificates. Issue certificates.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which statements about key escrow are true?",
              "answer":
                  "A third party has a copy or access to your private keys.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which statements are true about pinning?",
              "answer":
                  "An entire certificate can be pinned. Public key pinning is the hardest to implement but the most flexible. Certification pinning is the easiest to implement but not flexible.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which is a method of verifying the status of a certificate and contains a time-stamped OCSP response with the original certificate?",
              "answer": "Certificate stapling.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which correctly describes the public key infrastructure?",
              "answer":
                  "It ensures that public keys are the real public keys of the associated entities.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Wireless Security Settings
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "What must a client provide when connecting to an open wireless network?",
              "answer": "Nothing",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which form of authentication requires installed certificates on the part of both the client and the wireless authentication service?",
              "answer": "EAP-TLS",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which wireless standards are required to protect data using CCMP encryption?",
              "answer": "WPA2 Personal. WPA2 Enterprise.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the difference between configuring a WPA2 PSK wireless network and configuring a WPA wireless network?",
              "answer": "The automatic use of AES-based CCMP encryption.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What does Wi-Fi protected Setup provide to a wireless network?",
              "answer": "Easier “bypass” access to a secured network.",
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the function of a wireless captive portal?",
              "answer":
                  "A branded web page gateway used before providing access to the network.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "By default, which TCP/IP port must be open between the RADIUS server and the wireless authentication when using WPA2 Enterprise authentication?",
              "answer": "1812",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which WI-FI protocol introduced TKIP encryption?",
              "answer": "WPA",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which options are true about wireless corporate networks?",
              "answer":
                  "Additional encryption requirements are placed on the network. Additional authentication requirements are placed on the network.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which restriction is typically placed on WPA on current generation access points?",
              "answer": "It is only available as a backup to WPA2",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is a requirement of connecting to a RADIUS server when using WPA Enterprise?",
              "answer":
                  "The connecting AP must be configured as a trusted RADIUS client.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of wireless authentication would most likely be used for an “easy-access” guest network?",
              "answer": "Open",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Analyzing output from security technologies
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which attacks are mitigated by a web application firewall?",
              "answer": "DoS. SQL injection.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which removable media option is triggered when the device is plugged in?",
              "answer": " Auto play.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the first step when implementing data loss prevention?",
              "answer": "Identify assets.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which functions are part of a United Threat Management solution?",
              "answer": "Intrusion prevention. Content filtering.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Users complain in the morning that an application that worked the day before no longer runs without crashing. What is the most likely cause of the problem?",
              "answer": "Update history.",
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the purpose of file hashing?",
              "answer": " Integrity.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Employee Windows laptops must block all incoming connections when the laptop is disconnected from the corporate network. What should you do?",
              "answer":
                  "Configure the private network profile. Configure the public network profile.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which application whitelisting option applies to a specific version of a file?",
              "answer": "Hash",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A new form of windows server-based malware is known to be active throughout the internet. What should be done on your windows servers?",
              "answer": "Update virus definitions.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Date execution prevention applies to which option?",
              "answer": "Memory",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which security solution is designed to monitor application activity and logs?",
              "answer": "Host intrusion detection system.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Deploying Mobile devices securely
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which mobile technology separates the device from the app and data, which is stored on managed corporate servers and can lower IT management cost and complexity, enhance data security, offer device agility, and improve device uptime?",
              "answer": "VDI",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement is true regarding geofencing and geolocation?",
              "answer":
                  "Geofencing can determine when a device moves out of an area. Geolocation is a point on a map. Geofencing is a square area on the map. Administrators can use geolocation to find a lost device.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which features allows an administrator or an owner of a mobile device to send a command that deletes data and apps?",
              "answer": "Remote wipe",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which option is considered on of the strongest and most secure biometrics, making it highly dependable and beneficial for banking transaction authentication?",
              "answer": " Iris recognition.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Match the mobile operating system to the associated feature.Siri-iOS. Cortana-Windows. App Store-iOS.",
              "answer":
                  "Play store-Android. Open source – Android. Closed source – Windows.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Full device encryption software for mobility should have its own authentication mechanisms or leverage enterprise MFA. Which option is the least optimal solution?",
              "answer": "Strong passwords.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which feature divides the personal and business apps with their associated data to enforce separation at the app level combined with data encryption?",
              "answer": "Containerization.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Push notification services originally allowed the server to push mail, calendar, and contact services to network users. Select if the statement is true or false?",
              "answer": "True",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which option is no valid locking mechanism for a mobile device?",
              "answer": "Time lock.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which mobility feature extends previous capabilities by allowing users to send photographs, videos, text messages over 160 characters, and other data?",
              "answer": " MMS.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which option is a complementary technology to VoLTE that employs IMS technology to provide a packet voice service that is delivered over IP using a Wi-Fi network?",
              "answer": " VoWi-Fi",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which Android-specific term refers to the process of installing applications without using the official marketplace?",
              "answer": "Sideloading.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Implementing secure protocols
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "What TCP service port does SSL/TLS most commonly use?",
              "answer": "443",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which mode of SNMPv3 uses a cryptographic HMAC to secure authentication credentials and provide integrity but not data encryption?",
              "answer": "AuthNoPriv",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which statement is false regarding FTPS?",
              "answer":
                  "It is an IETF designed version of FTP that provides secure data transfer over a SSH2 channel.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements are true regarding secure file transfer protocol (SFTP)?",
              "answer":
                  "It is also called SSH file transfer protocol. Both the commands and data are encrypted. It is slower than SCP but platform independent.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which protocol is vulnerable to the MONLIST attack in the recent past?",
              "answer": "NTPv3",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which protocol is based on X.500 but is lighter cross-platform and standard-based solution that runs securely over SSL/TLS?",
              "answer": "LDAP",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which statement is false regarding the SSH2?",
              "answer":
                  "SSH2 uses asymmetric encryption for the bulk data encryption and symmetric algorithms for the key management processes.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which security services are provided by the S/MIME?",
              "answer": "Message encryption.\nDigital Signatures.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which protocol- released in 2004 by Cisco systems and Ericsson – uses variants of the advanced encryption algorithm to encrypt and decrypt all incoming and outgoing data?",
              "answer": "SRTP",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "You are configuring routing protocol authentication for two OSPF neighbor routers. When the sender needs to send an advertisement, what is originally combined with the message to generate the MAC?",
              "answer": "The sender’s copy of the shared secret.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What does the green lock icon on the address bar of the web browser mean?",
              "answer":
                  "It signifies that the web site has presented your browser with an extended validation certificate (EV)",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which protocol connects to the server using SSL/TLS on well-known TCP port 995?",
              "answer": "POPS",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which options are true concerning DNSSEC?",
              "answer":
                  "DNNSSEC protects users from DNS attacks and forces systems to detect DNS attacks. Validation is done using chain of trust where each response is signed. DNSSEC stands for DNS security extensions.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Trouble shooting common security issues
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which acronyms would best represent a system where a user enters a secured area by first displaying a badge to a camera, then entering a PIN in keypad, and finally having iris scanned?",
              "answer": "MFA",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which option is not a common reason for web browser security warnings?",
              "answer": "Using persistent self-signed certificate on server.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which controls would least likely help to prevent weak security configuration of systems and applications?",
              "answer": "Armed guards",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "How would you classify several warning log entries on your syslog server combined with an IPS sensor block to a router that is caused by a system auditor running a scheduled vulnerability scan against your intranet web servers?",
              "answer": "False positive",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement is false concerning configuration items, CI?",
              "answer":
                  "All RFID and GPS tracking methods should be deprecated.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Reduction in baseline deviation can be accomplished by using disk quotas, provisioned device usage quotas, and acceptable use. Select is this statement is true or false.",
              "answer": "True",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which options are considered the best practices for software license compliance?",
              "answer":
                  "Collect and store all licensing records and keys. Use an inventory system. Perform audits and release reports. Completely dispose off old software code and keys.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which option is not well-known personal cloud service?",
              "answer": "Kali",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement is false concerning personnel issues?",
              "answer":
                  "Safely terminate employees through e-mail or SMS whenever possible",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which system should be used in medium to larger organizations to manage mobile app software?",
              "answer": "MDM",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement is true regarding access violations?",
              "answer":
                  "Over time, the least privilege principle tends to degrade.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements are true concerning misconfigured devices and components?",
              "answer":
                  "Development, QA, and production environments may not be configured the same way. Configured and change management databases are vital for larger businesses. Running periodic scans can help to discover future possible misconfigurations. Unnecessary features and services are often installed or enabled.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement is false regarding recommendations for permission configuration on your network operating system?",
              "answer":
                  "Use the everyone groups as often as possible for access control simplicity.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which options are considered cleartext protocols?",
              "answer": "TELNET\nSMTP\nFTP\nHTTP",
            },
            {
              "question": "",
              "answer": "",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Identity Concepts and Access Services
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which Kerberos-trusted third-party service, familiar with all systems and trusted by all, guarantees privacy and data integrity?",
              "answer": "KDC",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which technique is used by CHAP to validate the identity of a person while maintaining the privacy of the shared secret password between the participating parties?",
              "answer": "Challenge/response.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following options are valid authentication factors?",
              "answer":
                  "Something you are. Something you have. Something you know.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which language is used by many cloud SSO connections for thousands of large enterprises, government agencies, and service providers that communicate on the internet?",
              "answer": "SAML",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Secure tokens may store which of the following components?",
              "answer":
                  "Cryptographic keys\nDigital signature\nPINs\nBiometric data\nPasswords",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which client-server protocol enables a remote access server to communicate with a central server to authenticate dial-in-users and authorize their access to systems?",
              "answer": "RADIUS",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which statement is not true about OAuth 2.0?",
              "answer":
                  "It is proprietary framework that allows any application complete access to HTTPS service.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which statement is false regarding TACACS+?",
              "answer":
                  "It combines the authentication and authorization message.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which protocol that verifies the end-user, is a basic identity layer on top of the OAuth 2.0 protocol?",
              "answer": "OpenID connect.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "All identity and authentication must be tied to an IP address. True or False?",
              "answer": "False",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "NTLM credentials are based on data obtained during the interactive logon process. Which option is not part pf of the NTLM credentials?",
              "answer": "Domain controller doing authentication.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which protocol provides secure interactive read/write management access to an X 500 or active Directory service?",
              "answer": "LDAPS",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which option is a free and open source that provides federated identity services for both inter and intra-organizational applications and services?",
              "answer": "Shibboleth.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Identity and Access management controls
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "The least privilege principle should be in place with file system security?\nSelect if the statement is true or false?",
              "answer": "True",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which option best represents the access control model that allows management access to a router form 6 A.M to 6 P.M, Monday through Friday, on particular virtual terminal lines that are configured using a time-based ACL?",
              "answer": "Rule-based.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements are correct regarding discretionary access controls?",
              "answer":
                  "DAC aligns with the least privilege security principle. DAC is easy to implement and operate. DAC allows the object owner to have control ever granted access.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which behavioral biometric leverages the aural aspects of speech that diverge among people?",
              "answer": "Speaker recognition.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement is false regarding facial recognition?",
              "answer":
                  "Is only used to identify individuals in video but not still images.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "La Bell-LaPadula model is an example of what kind of access control methodology?",
              "answer": "Mandatory Access Control (MAC).",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which mechanism measures the probability that the biometric system will incorrectly accept an access effort by an unauthorized user?",
              "answer": "FAR",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Database security should offer authorized and safe access for users and administrators while preventing the integrity of the date. Which option is not a key area of consideration?",
              "answer": "Making sure that all data is stored in the cloud.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What would be the best access model for a medical center where different categories of users such as doctors, RN, PA, technician, and receptionist need access assigned by an administrator based on the least privilege of their daily duties and responsibilities?",
              "answer": "RBAC",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "When presented with a certificate, the authentication server will at the minimum want to determine which of the following?",
              "answer":
                  "If the client has presented a proof of possession. If the certificate is expired based on timestamp. If the certificate is signed by a third- party trust point. If the certificate has been revoked by CRL or OCSP.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which term describes a small hardware device that the owner carries to get authorized access to a system or service?",
              "answer": "Token",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "ABAC relies on the evaluation of several factors in order to function properly. Which option is not a primary factor?",
              "answer": "Organizational role and responsibility.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement is not true concerning fingerprint scanning biometrics?",
              "answer":
                  "Not a common biometric as the fingerprint tend to change overtime.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Common Account Management Practices
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which options represent location-based policies that are a part of the context-based identity service methodologies?",
              "answer":
                  "Role-based authorization. Geographical location. Device profile and posture.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement is not an account maintenance best practice?",
              "answer":
                  "Shared user accounts should have passwords at least five characters long.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which option is not a common type of privileged account?",
              "answer": "Guest account.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which types of user accounts, required by the system, are often overlooked as being shared accounts because often only the system administrators have access to them?",
              "answer": "Shared administrative accounts.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The diversity of security models and policies make credential management particularly challenging.",
              "answer": "True.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which option is not a form of audit or review?",
              "answer": "Temporary.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which option is not considered a password best practice?",
              "answer": "Avoid MFA in favor of password mangers.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which account Is used by an application to function= with the network operating system and have passwords that are often rarely changed leading to significant vulnerability?",
              "answer": "Service accounts.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement describe the best practices for user accounts?",
              "answer":
                  "They should be unique per person and not shared. Admins should have a separate nonprivileged account for normal activities. It is best when they are centrally managed. It should employ least privilege security principles.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What do you call the process of issuing new certificates to need users and systems that have expired digital certificates?",
              "answer": "Recertifications.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which security principle apply a need to know scheme to trust relationships between users and security domains?",
              "answer": "Least privilege.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Cloud identity management will eventually replace the group-based and enterprise group policy approach.",
              "answer": "Onboarding.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Frameworks, Guidelines, and physical Security
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question": "Which type of light is best used in areas with fog?",
              "answer": "Sodium Vapor",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which frameworks are used to ensure that your organization is complying with governing laws and regulations?",
              "answer": "National. Regulatory. International.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which of the following statements are true?",
              "answer":
                  "A mantrap is designed to prevent piggybacking. A class II gate is used in commercial applications such as parking lots and garages",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which motion detection system uses radio waves to detect motion?",
              "answer": "Microwave.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement correctly defines the purpose of an airgap?",
              "answer":
                  "It is the concept of providing physical separation between a highly secure network and all other networks.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Why is vendor diversity considered a defence in depth strategy?",
              "answer":
                  "If one vendor’s product is compromised, the product from other vendors will not be compromised.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which options are considered as biometric authentication options?",
              "answer": "Odour. Keyboard dynamics. Fingerprint",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement best describes the purpose of vendor-specific security configuration guidelines?",
              "answer":
                  "To ensure the vendors product is deployed by the customer in the most secure manner.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which term describes an alarm that is triggered even though no malicious even has occurred?",
              "answer": "False positive.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following is used to protect devices from electromagnetic fields?",
              "answer": "Faraday cage.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of fire extinguisher is used to suppress combustible liquids such as a petroleum product?",
              "answer": "Type B",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What are the reasons for implementing physical security controls in the organization?",
              "answer":
                  "To protect your organization for environmental threats. To protect your organization from man-made threats. To protect your organization from political threats.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What type of lock uses pins that must be moved to create a shear line so that a plug can be turned to operate the lock?",
              "answer": "Pin tumbler.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What would you use to protect valuable items such as currency or deeds?",
              "answer": "Safe.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Implement Secure Network Architecture concepts
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question": "Which option best describes a honeypot?",
              "answer":
                  "An isolated site with services and data that appear to be of value to an attacker so they are enticed to connect to it.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which statements about VPNs are true?",
              "answer":
                  "A remote access VPN requires the client devices to have VPN software installed. A site- to-site VPN is typically used to connect two different sited together over an untrusted network. VPNs can be secured with IPsec or SSL.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which option best describes virtualization?",
              "answer":
                  "The practice of placing resources on the same physical product but logically separating them form each other.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which is the best location to place firewalls within your organization?",
              "answer":
                  "Anywhere you need to control the flow of traffic between zones in your organization.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "You are analyzing an SDN solution but want to make sure you have considered all possible communication security risks between the various SDN components. What should you be considering?",
              "answer":
                  "Communication between the applications and the controllers. Communication between any redundant controllers. Communication between the controllers and the network devices. Communication between the management stations and the controllers.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Secure system and Application Design and Deployment
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "A smartphone is seized as an evidence at a crime scene. What is used to prevent in and outbound communications for the smartphone?",
              "answer": "Faraday Cage.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What type of error can be detected at program runtime?",
              "answer": "Logic.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which term describes an operating system that is designed with enhanced security?",
              "answer": "Trusted OS.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which code testing technique uses an isolated environment?",
              "answer": "Sandboxing.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which development tool feature tracks code changes?",
              "answer": "Version control.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which term describes replacing systems and components instead of reconfiguring them?",
              "answer": "Immutable.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "You have installed a new IoT home automation and security system. What should you do to secure this environment?",
              "answer":
                  "Place IoT devices on an isolated network. Patch IoT firmware",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What should be configured to prevent unauthorized users from accessing data on the USB thumb drives?",
              "answer": "Encryption.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What should be established to detect deviations from normal configurations that can affect security?",
              "answer": "Secure baseline.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which technique is used to prove that the author of the code is authentic and that integrity has been ensured?",
              "answer": "Code signing.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which development life circle model relies on customer input throughout the entire system development process?",
              "answer": "Agile.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which security control prevents a single person form controlling an entire business process?",
              "answer": "Separation of duties.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which device relieves the CPU form encryption and decryption processing?",
              "answer": "HSM.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which term describes operating system software components that are stored on a circuit board?",
              "answer": "System on a chip.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A technician installs a Linux virtual machine form the installations media and then applies the latest operating system patches. What else should be done to harden the installation?",
              "answer":
                  "Disable unnecessary services. Configure a host-based firewall.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which mechanism is used by UEFI to determine if a boot environment change has been made?",
              "answer": "Hashing.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What software solution collects and analyzes data from sensors in an industrial environment?",
              "answer": "SCADA.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Cloud, Virtualization, and Resiliency Concepts
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the purpose of a cloud access security broker?",
              "answer":
                  "To extend your enterprise security policies into your own cloud solution.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which RAID levels provide resiliency and fault tolerance?",
              "answer": "RAID 6. RAID 5. RAID 1.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which statements are true?",
              "answer":
                  "When using a VDI, the PC requires very little CPU and memory to operate. When using a VDI, the local devices desktop is stored as a VM on a server in a datacenter",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement best describes the automated courses of action?",
              "answer":
                  "Automated actions that take place when a cyber-attack occurs.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which cloud solutions will have servers, storage, and networking that are managed by the provider an applications, data, and operating systems that are managed by the customer?",
              "answer": "IaaS.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which options will reduce human error when repetition exists?",
              "answer": "Scripts, Templates. Master image.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "How do you protect your virtual machines from VM escape? ",
              "answer":
                  "Install verified and trusted applications. Patch VMs and software regularly. Control access to VMs.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which option describes the ability of a system to adapt to the current demands by provisioning and deprovisioning resources as needed?",
              "answer": "Elasticity.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which option is an image of the table of a system taken at a specific point in time?",
              "answer": "Snapshot.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What type of hypervisor runs directly on top of a bare-metal servers’ hardware?",
              "answer": "Type 1",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which statements are true?",
              "answer":
                  "Fault tolerance is defined as continued operation when failures occur. Redundancy is achieved through the duplication of critical components. High availability is achieved through redundancy.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Policies, Plans, and Procedures
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which administrative job control was designed so that collusion would have to occur for a crime to be committed?",
              "answer": "Separation of duties.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which option is a legal contract between two or more parties that outlines which information can and cannot be shared with others?",
              "answer": "NDA.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which is the easiest way to reduce the likelihood of an attack that originates from inside your organization?",
              "answer":
                  "Provide all users in the organization with security awareness training.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What policy is used to inform users about their expected behavior when referencing the organization while using twitter or Facebook?",
              "answer": "Social media policy.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which option identifies how employees are expected to use resources in the organization?",
              "answer": "AUP.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of agreement outlines the responsibilities of each organization for the connection that will be established?",
              "answer": "MoU.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which options are achieved by implementing a SOP?",
              "answer":
                  "Users will be able to perform tasks in an efficient order. There is a greater chance that regulations will be met. The quality of the work performed by the users will improve.",
            },
          ]
        },
        // Business Impact Analysis and Risk Management
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "A malicious user intentionally takes advantage of a wireless router weakness. Which term describes this cation?",
              "answer": "Exploit.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Proper change management procedures must document activities. Where are these activities documented?",
              "answer": "Change log.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which activity determines if PII is being handled properly?",
              "answer": "Privacy impact assessment.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which type of analysis is based on monetary values?",
              "answer": "Quantitative analysis.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which term relates to how long it takes to restore a service or business function?",
              "answer": "RTO.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which term describes the amount of time between failure of a service, components, or business process?",
              "answer": "MTBF",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Your company requires a report identifying IT weaknesses on the network for regulatory compliance so that the security controls can be put in place. What should be done?",
              "answer": "Vulnerability assessment.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Your company purchases a cyber insurance policy for web site protection against DDoS attacks. What type of risk response is this?",
              "answer": "Risk transfer.",
            },
            {
              "question": "How is residual risk defined?",
              "answer": "Total risk minus safeguard.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of document maps put how a business can resume operations as quickly as possible in the event of a disaster?",
              "answer": "Business continuity plan.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of document focuses on how negative incidents affect an organization?",
              "answer": "Business impact analysis.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which threat attribute is used to assign priorities?.",
              "answer": "Likelihood of occurrence.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which term describes a central repository of identified risks?",
              "answer": "Risk registry",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which type pf analysis id based on expert opinions?",
              "answer": "Qualitative risk analysis.",
            },
          ]
        },
        // Incident response, Forensics, and Disaster Recovery
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "How do strategic intelligence and strategic counterintelligence differ?",
              "answer":
                  "Strategic intelligence focuses on past trends and patterns.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Your company enables cloud archiving with immutability. What does this configuration mean?",
              "answer": "Archived data cannot be modified.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which options are related to the disaster recovery plans?",
              "answer": "Hot site. Server reimaging.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which option is deterrent control?",
              "answer": "Fence.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which security component is address with georeplication?",
              "answer": "Availability.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which deletion technique overwrites the disk sectors with 1s and 0s?",
              "answer": "Wiping.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A court order necessitates the seizure of an on-premises server containing potential evidence for a court case. What has been placed on the server?",
              "answer": "Legal hold.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which term describes the sensitive patient medical information?",
              "answer": "PHI",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Choose the correct order of volatility from most to least volatile.",
              "answer": "CPU cache, RAM",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of alternate site has up to date data that is replicated form a primary site?",
              "answer": "Hot.",
            },
            {
              "question": "What data role maintains CIA?",
              "answer": "Custodian.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which term stems from the documentation related top a completed incident?",
              "answer": "Lessons learned",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of backup backs up only the new or modified data from the last full back up?",
              "answer": "Differential.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which term describes the entity that is responsible for dealing with IT-related events?",
              "answer": "Cyber incidents response team.",
            },
          ]
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Networking",
      "items": [
        // Network
        "Ports and protocols and the OSI Model",
        "Routing Switching and IP Addressing",
        "Network Topologies & Technologies",
        "Cloud concepts, network services, & cabling",
        "Networking Device",
        "Network storage, Virtualization, &WAN Technologies",
        "Documentation and Diagrams & Business Continuity",
        "Network Monitoring & Remote Access Methods",
        "Policies and Best practices",
        "Security Devices, Wireless Security, & Access Control",
        "Network attacks & device hardening",
        "Mitigation Techniques",
        "Troubleshooting Methodology & Tools",
        "Troubleshooting Connectivity & Performance",
        "Troubleshooting common network service issues",
      ],
      "questions": [
        /**************************************
     *    Network_study guide.pdf
    **************************************/
        {
          // Ports and protocols and the OSI Model
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which networking functions occur at the Network layer of the OSI Model?",
              "answer": "Logical addressing, Routing, Fragmentation.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which protocols are operated at the Application layer of the OSI Model?",
              "answer": "HTTP, DNS, FTP.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The OSI Model was designed to facilitate which objective?",
              "answer":
                  "Consistency and compatibility when developing new network applications, protocols, and devices. ",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The data link layer of the OSI Model is subdivided into which other layers?",
              "answer": "LLC, MAC.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of network activities are handled by the session layer of the OSI Model?",
              "answer": "Logins, Name recognition.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Match the protocol to its appropriate port?",
              "answer":
                  "Trivial File Transfer Protocol: port 69. Hypertext Transfer protocol secure: port 443. Domain name system: port 53. Simple Mail transfer protocol: port 25. Remote desktop protocol: port 3389. Hypertext Transfer Protocol: 80.",
            },
            {
              "question": "User Datagram Protocol?",
              "answer": "Is faster than TCP and is a connectionless protocol.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which objects operate at the physical layer of the OSI Model?",
              "answer": "Hubs, repeaters, cables.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of network activities are handled by the presentation layer of the OSI Model?",
              "answer":
                  "Compression and encryption, Character code translation.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements about the transmission control protocol are correct?",
              "answer":
                  "It provides guaranteed delivery of packets, it uses acknowledgements.",
            },
            {
              "question": "IP resides at which layer of the OSI model?",
              "answer": "Network.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements about connection-oriented protocols are correct?",
              "answer":
                  "TCP is the preferred transport protocol; Preliminary negotiations are used to setup and establish end to end communication.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements about connectionless protocols are correct?",
              "answer":
                  "No prior arrangements are made between endpoints before sending data, it is less reliable but faster, UDP is the preferred transport protocol.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which network communication characteristic is determined at the transport layer of the OSI Model?",
              "answer": "Connection oriented vs connectionless communication.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which TCP/IP diagnostic utilities make use of ICMP?",
              "answer": "Traceroute, ping.",
            },
          ]
        },
        //Routing Switching and IP Addressing
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Performance concepts such as traffic shaping. QoS and DiffServ are primarily concerned with providing what kind of service?",
              "answer": "Prioritizing packets by importance.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "If there are 6 bits available to address host systems in a network, how many hosts can you accommodate?",
              "answer": "64",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement about default gateways and subnet masks are correct?",
              "answer":
                  "The default subnet mask is dependent on the class of your network. A default gateway is only required if access to external networks in necessary. A subnet mask is always required.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "How many subnets are created by the subnet mask 255 255 255 192?",
              "answer": "4",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which IP addresses are considered to be private addresses?",
              "answer": "10.0.0.1, 169.254.0.1, 192.168.0.1",
            },
            {
              "question": "A broadcast domain is ended by which object?",
              "answer": "Router",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements are correct about isolating networks using a router vs. isolating segments using a switch?",
              "answer":
                  "Switches isolate each segment by filtering based on the MAC address. Routers are not concerned with directly connecting hosts only networks. Routers isolate each network by filtering based on the IP address.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of transmission would be used if an application needed to send packets to every other host on your network?",
              "answer": "Broadcast",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which subnet mask would be used to supernet 2 class C networks together into a single subnet with 512 hosts?",
              "answer": "255.255.254.0",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which network segmentation method uses a combination of firewalls to protect internal resources from external threats?",
              "answer": "DMZ",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which subnet mask is required to create subnets capable of hosting approximately 2000 hosts?",
              "answer": "255.255.248.0",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which protocol might send packets over a longer route if there is less traffic on that route?",
              "answer": "OSPF",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The term “dual stack” refers to which feature of TCP/IP?",
              "answer":
                  "That both versions 4 and 6 are installed, and either can be used.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements are correct about a virtual IP address?",
              "answer":
                  "It is an address that does not correspond to a specific or physical interface. It is a value assigned to a group of servers such as a cluster or a load-balanced set.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which process will automatically assign an address of 169.254.x.x to a system in the event it is unable to contact a DHCP server?",
              "answer": "APIPA",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Port forwarding is commonly used in which types of applications?",
              "answer":
                  "Voice over IP applications. Online gaming servers.Peer to peer downloading.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which subnet mask is commonly used in class A networks to make them the size of a class C network?",
              "answer":
                  "To restrict updates for routers to only specific interfaces. To enable basic security for a network.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the range of addresses for the first subnet created by using the subnet mask of 255.255.255.192 in the 192.168.0.0 class C network?",
              "answer": "192.168.0.0 – 192.168.0.68",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which conversion is an example of network address translation?",
              "answer": "10.0.0.03 to 129.1.2.3",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which binary value represents the decimal value of 192?",
              "answer": "11000000.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which address is used as the loopback address in TCP/IP diagnostics?",
              "answer": "127.0.0.1",
            },
          ]
        },
        // Network Topologies & Technologies
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Multiple input multiple output (MIMO) is supported by which 802.11 specifications?",
              "answer": "ac. N",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of network configuration is typically implemented for a large company with multiple branch offices in the same general geographic region such as a city?",
              "answer": "MAN",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which advantages do 2.4 GHz transmission have over 5GHz transmissions?",
              "answer":
                  "They have a wider signal coverage area. They are more compatible with older services. They are better at penetrating obstacles and barriers.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "if one wireless router is using channel 6 to setup an additional router using a different channel, which would be the best channel to use?",
              "answer": "11",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which statement best describes CDMA?",
              "answer": "A multiplexing method based on coded signals.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type pf network configuration can be created with as little as a wireless router and a connection to an ISP?",
              "answer": "Ad-hoc.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Channel bonding refers to which process?",
              "answer":
                  "Combining the bandwidth of multiple channels to increase throughput.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which 802.11 specification uses 2.4 GHz transmissions and offers a speed up to 54 Mbps over a distance of approximately 150 feet?",
              "answer": "G",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of antenna is the most precise in terms of directional communications?",
              "answer": "Yagi-Uda.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which internet of things (Iot) protocol is typically used for home automation?",
              "answer": "Z-wave",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which network apology is the most complex, but also the most reliable?",
              "answer": "Mesh",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of site survey is done without any actual field measurements?",
              "answer": "Predictive",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which 802.11 specification supports simultaneous connections of 2.4 GHz and 5 GHz transmissions?",
              "answer": "Ac",
            },
          ]
        },
        // Cloud concepts, network services, & cabling
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "IPAM is responsible for providing which type of network service?",
              "answer":
                  "Administration and monitoring of DHCP and DNS servers.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The “T” in 100Base T stands for which cable characteristic?",
              "answer": "Twisted Pair Cabling",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which copper cable connector is most commonly used in today’s network connections?",
              "answer": "RJ-45",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which termination point uses standard RJ-45 connections?",
              "answer": "Patch panel",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The most accurate time sources available by standard network connections reside at which stratum of the network time protocol?",
              "answer": "1",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A DHCP client will not begin using its assigned IP address until which type of transmission has been received?",
              "answer": "DHCPAck",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of cloud service connectivity method would typically allow for unlimited data transfers once implemented?",
              "answer": "Direct Connection",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "“Data pooling” refers to which public could risk considerations?",
              "answer":
                  "Infrastructure is shared by multiple tenants. No commo concerns or interests for security.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Plenum cable is sometimes used over PVC cable because of which characteristic?",
              "answer": "Resistance to fire.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which fiber cable connect is preferred when the least amount of return loss (reflection) is required?",
              "answer": "APC",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Components and their appropriate to their cloud service type?",
              "answer":
                  "Software Development Environment – PaaS, Virtual Machine and operating systems – IaaS, Enterprise Resourceplanning application and Customer Management application – SaaS.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The DNS service is responsible for which type of resolution?",
              "answer": "Host name to IP address.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which local storage characteristics would be considered to be benefits over cloud storage?",
              "answer":
                  "It offers better control of backups and access. It is faster.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of DNS record must be created to be able to send and receive internet email?",
              "answer": "MX",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which property if a start of authority record indicates the validity period for the name registration?",
              "answer": "Expiration time.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of cloud service typically offers the highest levels of control, customization and data transfer rates?",
              "answer": "Private",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which part of the fully qualified domain name of “mailsery.east.brocadero.com” indicates the subdomain?",
              "answer": "East",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which primary enhancement is offered by an SFP+ transceiver over an SFP or a GBIC transceiver?",
              "answer": "Faster transmission rates.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of cabling consists of 4 pairs of twisted pair copper wire covered by a protective shielding?",
              "answer": "STP",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which ethernet cable category was the first to support gigabit transfer rates?",
              "answer": "5e",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Networking Device
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "A load balancer can provide which networking features?",
              "answer":
                  "Even distribution of traffic across servers performing the same function. Improved performance and availability by ensuring servers do not become overwhelmed.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A multi layered switch operates over which 2 layers?",
              "answer": "2 and 3",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which characteristics of a switch distinguish it from a hub?",
              "answer":
                  "Switches forward traffic based on the MAC Address. Switches operate at layer 2 of the OSI model, hubs operate at layer 1",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of device is able to stop activity that is considered to be suspicious based on historical traffic patterns?",
              "answer": "Intrusion Prevention System.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which device could be classified as a next generation firewall?",
              "answer": "UTM",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which characteristics of a bridge distinguish if from a switch?",
              "answer":
                  "Bridges can connect dissimilar architectures. Bridges can connect dissimilar types of media, Switches connect host systems together, bridges connect network segments.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A software firewall running on a windows 10 PC is an example of which type of firewall?",
              "answer": "Host-based",
            },
            {
              "question": "In which scenario would you implement a modem?",
              "answer": "To connect a host to the internet over a phone line.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which scenario would best warrant the implementation of a RADUIUS server?",
              "answer":
                  "When you have multiple network access servers, with a single authentication policy.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Routers operate at which layer of the OSI model?",
              "answer": "Network",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which types of wireless access points might be used by an attacker to gain access to confidential information?",
              "answer": "Evil twin.Rogue.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A president VPN that is established between two physical locations such as a branch attacker office to headquarters with VPN concentrators on both ends is an example of which type of VPN?",
              "answer": "Site-to-site.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Configuring radio balancing in a wireless controller refers to which feature?",
              "answer":
                  "Ensuring that all 802. 11n clients are connected to 802.11n access points.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A range extender is the wireless equivalent to which wired device?",
              "answer": "Repeater",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which security functions can be performed by a proxy server?",
              "answer":
                  "Packet examination and filtering. Shielding internal addresses from the public internet.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which types of conversions can be performed by media converters?",
              "answer":
                  "Electrical signals (copper wire) to light signals (fiber optic). Multi-mode fiber to single mode fiber.",
            },
            {
              "question": "VoIP phones make use of which transmission media?",
              "answer": "The Internet",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement best describes a unified threat management device?",
              "answer": "An all in one security device.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which of the following are characteristics of a VoIP gateway?",
              "answer": "Billing, Packetization, voice and fax compression.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Content filtering uses which primary method to screen objectionable content?",
              "answer": "Character strings",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Network storage, Virtualization, &WAN Technologies
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which Statements correctly describe the benefit of using jumbo frames when accessing storage?",
              "answer":
                  "Larger frames are more efficient and can reduce the amount of heat a device generates. A decreased number of frames reduces overall processing requirements.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which SAN component is responsible for identifying the storage available to any given system?",
              "answer": "LUN",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Targets and Initiators are components o9f which SAN protocol?",
              "answer": "iSCSI",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which protocol is used to access Network Attached Storage?",
              "answer": "TCP/IP",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of WAN service uses 2 dedicated phone lines to provide a bandwidth of approximately 128kbps?",
              "answer": "ISDN",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements about type 1 hypervisors are correct?",
              "answer":
                  "They generally perform better as they consume fewer system resources. They can be installed directly on top of hardware.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of service can route different protocols based on labels?",
              "answer": "MPLS.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A virtual machine requires which configuration to be able to network with other computers on the network?",
              "answer":
                  "A virtual adapter within the virtual machine, and access to the physical adapter on the host.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements correctly describe the characteristics of a demarcation point?",
              "answer":
                  "It marks the physical point where public and private network connections meet. It marks the boundary of responsibility for troubleshooting.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of WAN service would be most effective for real- time communications such as voice over IP and video conferencing?",
              "answer": "SDSL",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Sharing common internet connection over DSL is an example of which type of service?",
              "answer": "PPPoE",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the primary benefit of using satellite communications for WAN connectivity?",
              "answer": "Coverage area.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Documentation and Diagrams & Business Continuity
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Maintaining an effective inventory management process can assist with which tasks?",
              "answer":
                  "Planning and estimating network size. Keeping track of loss or theft of equipment.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which availability solution is not specifically designed for high availability, but provides it by default?",
              "answer": "Load balancing.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which option would you be most likely to see in a standard operating procedure document?",
              "answer":
                  "The identity of a person to contact for technical support.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Implementing a writing diagram can assist in which tasks?",
              "answer":
                  "Determining where cables terminate. Determining the location of wires running through plenum space.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Proposed changes to environment are typically outlined in which type of object?",
              "answer": "RFC",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The MTBF value of a device is typically derived from which factors?",
              "answer":
                  "Product experience/customer feedback. Product testing.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which power management/availability solution might you implement to address isolated outages and offer multiple connectivity paths within your data center?",
              "answer": "Redundant circuits",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A stand-by location that relies on existing backups and has some equipment and software available is referred to as which type of site?",
              "answer": "Warm site",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of backup backs up only data that has changed since the last full backup?",
              "answer": "Differential.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Information used to create a baseline of network performance should be gathered in which manner?",
              "answer": "Regularly- at varying times.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which types of objects should typically be included in a network diagram?",
              "answer": "Routers, servers, workstations.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the typical configuration for MDF and IDF devices?",
              "answer": "A single MDF, connected to multiple IDF.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The MTTF value of a device refers to which characteristic?",
              "answer":
                  "A point after which device is no longer considered to be reliable.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which option would you be most likely to see in a logical network diagram?",
              "answer": "The addressing scheme of your subnets.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Implementing a rack diagram can assist in which task?",
              "answer":
                  "Quickly determine which equipment is necessary when purchasing.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In which labeling scenario would you typically find cable tags?",
              "answer": "Bundling a group of related cables together.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What percentage of uptime is commonly offered by most service providers in an SLA?",
              "answer": "99.99",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Network Monitoring & Remote Access Methods
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question": "Rolling back an update refers to which process?",
              "answer":
                  "Removing an update that has been determined to be unstable or problematic.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which characteristics distinguish TFTP from FTP and FTPS?",
              "answer":
                  "Its is a simplified version of FTP. It uses UDP as its transport protocol.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which characteristics of the remote desktop protocol are correct?",
              "answer":
                  "It is a proprietary protocol developed by Microsoft. It is designed to provide remote access to a computer’s desktop.",
            },
            {
              "question": "HTTPS is secured by which protocols?",
              "answer": "TLS. SSL",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What types of objects are typically monitored using SNMP?",
              "answer": "Routers, servers, printers, Network Utilization.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Telnet is still used in which types of scenarios?",
              "answer":
                  "Configuring a router. Passing local commands to be executed on a remote system.",
            },
            {
              "question": "The term “ethical hacking” refers to which process?",
              "answer":
                  "Attempting to intrude into a network to identify weaknesses to be addressed.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which remote access protocol would be best suited to sharing a demonstration on your computer with multiple other users in real time?",
              "answer": "VNC",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which characteristics correctly describe an event notification?",
              "answer":
                  "Someone is always informed. They are generally based on a pre- determined threshold.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Out-of-hand management refers to which process?",
              "answer":
                  "Implementing redundancy to allow for continued network management in the event of failure.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Secret Shell (SSH) operates over which port by default?",
              "answer": "22",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The percentage of data must be retransmitted on a network due to communications failure is known as what",
              "answer": "Packet Loss",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which statement best describes a host-to-site VPN?",
              "answer":
                  "A user- initiated VPN configured between their local system and the organization’s LAN.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Policies and Best practices
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statements about password usage and policies are correct?",
              "answer":
                  "Passwords should be longer in length to make them harder to guess.Passwords should be changed regularly.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which tasks would be associated with onboarding a new employee?",
              "answer":
                  "Setup an email address. Grant access to network shares.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of documentation outlines how a business collects, uses, shares, and stores information?",
              "answer": "Privacy Policy.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Privileged access is typically granted to which types of users?",
              "answer": "Network administrators. Selected departmental staff.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In today’s business and computing environment import/export controls generally only apply to which tiers of country?",
              "answer": "4, 3",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A remote access policy might typically define which connectivity characteristics?",
              "answer": "The type of device you can use to connect.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Incident response policies are generally implemented to respond to which types of incidents?",
              "answer": "Security breaches.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In which scenario might you choose to implement a non-disclosure agreement?",
              "answer":
                  "To ensure legal consequences are in place should an employee reveal confidential information.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of software licensing model is typically developed through public collaboration?",
              "answer": "Open source",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which mobile device management technique allows you to selectively wipe only corporate data while leaving personal data intact?",
              "answer": "Device partitioning/containerization.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A documented system life can be useful in which situations?",
              "answer": "When determining budgets and allocation of resources.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Security Devices, Wireless Security, & Access Control
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Shining a laser or a bright flashlight directly into a security camera would be classified as which type of interference?",
              "answer": "Defocusing",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Verifying for the presence of an antivirus application on a system before allowing connectivity would be an example of which type of access control?",
              "answer": "Network Access Control (NAC)",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which options should typically be included in a software asset management implementation?",
              "answer": "License overages. Mobile device operating systems.",
            },
            {
              "question": "TKIP-RC4 had which primary benefits?",
              "answer":
                  "It was compatible with devices that supported WEP. It offered better security than WEP.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In multifactor authentication, a fingerprint would be classified as which option?",
              "answer": "Something you are.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Temporal Key integrity protocol (TKIP) was the primary encryption method in which wireless security implementation?",
              "answer": "WPA",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which wireless authentication method involves maintaining a list of authorized addresses?",
              "answer": "MAC filtering.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of security camera would you likely see mounted on the ceiling of a bank or other secure location?",
              "answer": "Dome",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which options would be considered to be biometric methods of authentication?",
              "answer": "Retina scan. Fingerprint.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Lightweight Directory Access Protocol (LDAP) is used for which purpose?",
              "answer":
                  "Establishing communication form an application to a network directory service.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In which scenarios might you choose to implement geofencing?",
              "answer":
                  "Notifying an administrator if an unauthorized user enters a secure location. Tracking the movement of a corporately owned device.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which process is concerned only with establishing the identity of a user or device?",
              "answer": "Authentication",
            },
          ]
        },
        // Network attacks & device hardening
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "A man-in-the-middle attack that downgrades a secure connection to an insecure one is know as which option?",
              "answer": "SSL Stripping",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of attack is designed to damage a system to the point of it generally needing to be replaced?",
              "answer": "PDoS",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In second or multi-factor authentication, a PIN would be categorized how?",
              "answer": "Something you know.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which characteristic distinguishes a logic bomb form other types of threats?",
              "answer":
                  "The code remains dormant for a period of time after infection.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Patch management and phased deployment of updates should be implemented to avoid which possible problems?",
              "answer":
                  "Rebooting at an inconvenient time. Causing excessive network traffic.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which phase of the key generation life cycle involves backing up or archiving a key?",
              "answer": "Post activation.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Hashing is used to detect which type of possible security breach?",
              "answer": "Unauthorized changes to a file.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which term refers to the study of cryptographic systems?",
              "answer": "Cryptoanalysis",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Disabling ports on a switch or a router can help to protect against which type of attack?",
              "answer": "Unauthorized physical access to the network.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "ARP poisoning is often used as part of which type of threats or attacks?",
              "answer":
                  "Session hijacking. Man-in-the-middle. Denial of service.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which option best describes ransomware?",
              "answer":
                  "Maliciously encrypting data and demanding payment for the decryption key.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which secure protocol was introduced as the replacement for secure sockets layer (SSL)?",
              "answer": "TLS",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A brute force attack is characterized by which option?",
              "answer":
                  "Attempting all possible values or combinations to obtain a password or decryption key.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Social engineering attacks are based on misusing or exploiting which vulnerability?",
              "answer": "User trust.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of user might you initially suspect if an insider threat was discovered?",
              "answer": "The Network administrator.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Before you can properly identify threats, you must also identity what?",
              "answer": "Assets",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Searching for any available wireless network signal in attempt to exploit the network is known as which type of threat?",
              "answer": "Wardriving",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The process of reducing your attack surface by disabling unnecessary services is knows as what?",
              "answer": "Hardening",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Trusted platform Modules (TPM) and up-to-date firmware can help to protect against which types of threats?",
              "answer": "Rootkits/bootkits",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which option best describes spoofing?",
              "answer": "Forging the contents of data packets.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Mitigation Techniques
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which behaviors would be examples of applying the principle of least privilege?",
              "answer":
                  "A desktop support technician being granted the permission to install software. A departmental technical user being given only the ability to reset passwords in that department.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Separation of duties is typically implemented to achieve which goal?",
              "answer":
                  "To ensure that no single individual has complete control over an administrative environment.",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which statement correctly describes a Native VLAN?",
              "answer": "It is the only VLAN to not receive a tag.",
            },
            {
              "question": "File integrity refers ton which process?",
              "answer": "Protecting a file from unauthorized changes.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which network segmentation method places systems in a perimeter network between the internet and an internal network?",
              "answer": "DMZ",
            },
            {
              "question": "Which statement best describes a honeypot?",
              "answer": "A decoy system used to lure attackers.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Virus signatures are identified by anti-virus applications by using which techniques?",
              "answer": "Heuristic Engines. Algorithms/Hashing",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which actions would be considered to be device or host hardening techniques?",
              "answer":
                  "Deactivating default accounts. Disabling unnecessary services. Applying patches.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Permissions to a file system resource can be granted to which types of objects?",
              "answer": "Users. Groups. Computers.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which switch port protection method uses a whitelist of acceptable values to accept traffic?",
              "answer": "MAC filtering.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which statement characterizes a “black box” penetration test?",
              "answer": "The testers have no information about the target.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Sequence the switch port state transition method implemented by the spanning tree protocol?",
              "answer": "Blocking. Listening. Learning. Forwarding.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Troubleshooting Methodology & Tools
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which windows-based command line tool can be used to discard and request a new IP address configuration?",
              "answer": "Ipconfig",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which tool is used to characterize and find faults with fiber cabling?",
              "answer": "OTDR",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Documentation of an issue should include which values?",
              "answer":
                  "Outcomes. Corrective actions taken. Initial problem (date, reported by, scope)",
            },
            {
              "question": "Packets sniffing refers to which process?",
              "answer": "Intercepting and logging network traffic.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "What is the first goal of implementing a troubleshooting methodology?",
              "answer": "Identify the problem",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of port scanning method disguises the location of the sender?",
              "answer": "FTP bounce.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Establishing a theory of probable cause should involve which steps?",
              "answer":
                  "Prioritizing/categorizing the list of potential causes.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Most modern-day bandwidth speed testers are implemented in which manner?",
              "answer": "Through browsers.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A WIFI analyzer is typically used in which scenario?",
              "answer":
                  "Planning, surveying and mapping a new WIFI implementation.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Identifying potential effects of a plan of action refers to which possibility?",
              "answer": "That a plan may have unforeseen repercussions.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "When testing a theory of all probable causes yields no results what should generally be done next?",
              "answer": "Escalate the issue.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which linux-based command line tool can be used to capture packets for future analysis?",
              "answer": "Tcpdump",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Escalation of problem refers to implementing which approach?",
              "answer":
                  "Notifying the closest level of help, and moving up from there.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "After verifying system functionality has been restored, which additional step might also be taken?",
              "answer":
                  "Implement preventative measures to prevent the same problem form reoccurring.",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Troubleshooting Connectivity & Performance
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Scrambled or garbled communications when using VoIP or video conferencing applications is an indication of which type of network issue?",
              "answer": "Jitter",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which symptoms might be indicative of an intermittent short in a network environment?",
              "answer": "Periodic connectivity loss. Broadcast storms.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "By default, Which channels in a 2.4 GHz wireless network do not overlap?",
              "answer": "6, 11, 1",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A wireless signal having to move around a large object such as a hill or a building is known as which type of interference?",
              "answer": "Diffraction",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A flashing amber light on a network adapter might be indicative of which networking problem?",
              "answer": "Collisions",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "A hidden node normally occurs under which When nodes are close enough to the access point, but too far from each othercircumstances?",
              "answer":
                  "When nodes are close enough to the access point, but too far from each other",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which mitigation methods can be implemented to reduce the effects of network crosstalk?",
              "answer":
                  "Use shielded cables. Avoid sources of power when running cables",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "How many characters are used the passphrase when you have configured WPA/WPA2 for your wireless security?",
              "answer": "Any value between 8 and 63",
            },
            {
              "question": "A bottleneck is analogous to which situation?",
              "answer": "Highway traffic being reduced from 2 lanes to 1.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Why might you choose to implement a wireless network using the 5 GHz band as opposed to the 2.4 GHz band?",
              "answer": "It is generally less congested.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Rank the following obstructions (from lowest to highest) according to the amount of attenuation they can cause for wireless communications:",
              "answer":
                  "Glass windows. Wooden door. Drywall. Cinderblock. Brick wall. Concrete wall.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Auto negotiation can automatically configure which settings on a network adapter?",
              "answer": "Flow. Speed. Duplex mode.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "The measure of how much interference is present on a wireless network compared to the quality of the signal is known as what?",
              "answer": "Signal-to-noise ratio.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which step should generally be taken first when troubleshooting a suspected damaged cable?",
              "answer": "Replace the cable with a known good cable.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Rank the following wireless security configurations form least secure to most secure:",
              "answer": "Open. WEP. WPA+ TKIP. WPA2+TKIP/AES. WPA2 + AES.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of cable should be used to make a network connection form one computer directly to another computer?",
              "answer": "Crossover",
            },
          ],
        },
        // Troubleshooting common network service issues
        {
          "items": [
            {
              "question":
                  "Which problems might be encountered if a router’s ACL is misconfigured?",
              "answer":
                  "Legitimate traffic may be blocked. Unauthorized access may be granted.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "If a DHCP server is configured properly with a scope and the service is healthy yet still no addresses are being assigned what is the most likely cause?",
              "answer": "The scope has not been activated",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which type of address duplication conflict is most likely to happen in a network environment?",
              "answer":
                  "Two hosts configured with the same statically assigned IP address.",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which administrative tool can be used to view logged entries associated with service starts, crashes or failures?",
              "answer": "Event Viewer – System log",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which scenario would be best suited to a very short DHCP lease duration?",
              "answer": "A public Wifi area such as a coffee shop",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which troubleshooting tool provides detailed information about TLS handshake?",
              "answer": "Wireshark",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "In a default configuration of a class C subnet, which subnet mask should you assign to the clients?",
              "answer": "255.255.255.0",
            },
            {
              "question":
                  "Which command line tools can be used to test and troubleshoot DNS?",
              "answer": "Ping. Nslookup.",
            }
          ],
        },
      ]
    },
  ];

  List get topics {
    return [..._items];
  }
}
